[{"qid": "time_0_ab_en", "question": "Valentino Lazaro played for which team from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1_ab_en", "question": "Which team did the player Domenico Caso belong to between 1979 and 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_2_ab_en", "question": "Marco Ferrante played for which team in 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_3_ab_en", "question": "Federico Bonazzoli played for which team from 2013 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_4_ab_en", "question": "Which team did Luciano Bodini play for from 1990 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_5_ab_en", "question": "Which team did Mame Thiam play for between 2011 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_6_ab_en", "question": "Annibale Frossi played for which team from 1936 to 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_7_ab_en", "question": "Which team did Orazio Rancati play for from 1958 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_8_ab_en", "question": "Which team did the player Vampeta belong to in 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_9_ab_en", "question": "Silvio Pietroboni played for which team from 1919 to 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_10_ab_en", "question": "Filippo Mancini played for which team in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_11_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of George V from 1931 to 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_12_ab_en", "question": "What position did Prithvi Narayan Shah take between 1743 and 1768?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_13_ab_en", "question": "What position did Princess Zhejue take between 408 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_14_ab_en", "question": "What position did Po Tisuntiraidapuran take between 1786 and 1793?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_15_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Wuffa of East Anglia hold between 571 and 578?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_16_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of Po Tisuntiraidapuran between 1780 and 1781?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_17_ab_en", "question": "Ibrahim Njoya took which position from 1889 to 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_18_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of Gwangjong of Goryeo from 950 to 975?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_19_ab_en", "question": "Dokka Umarov took which position between 2007 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_20_ab_en", "question": "Alexander I of Scotland took which position from 1107 to 1124?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_21_ab_en", "question": "What position did Napoleon Louis Bonaparte take in 1810?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_22_ab_en", "question": "Ngawang Namgyal took which position from 1512 to 1544?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_23_ab_en", "question": "What position did Empress Matilda take in the year of 1141?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_24_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Gongyang of Goryeo hold from 1389 to 1392?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_25_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Edward the Elder hold between 918 and 924?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_26_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of Donyo between 1479 and 1512?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_27_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Chungnyeol hold between 1299 and 1308?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_28_ab_en", "question": "What position did Talorgan II take from 780 to 782?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_29_ab_en", "question": "Chungnyeol took which position between 1274 and 1298?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_30_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Ngwane V hold from 1895 to 1899?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_31_ab_en", "question": "What position did Levi Woodbury take from 1845 to 1851?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_32_ab_en", "question": "Jacques Delors took which position between 1985 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "President of the European Commission", "id": "Q8882"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_33_ab_en", "question": "What position did Jacques Santer take from 1995 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "President of the European Commission", "id": "Q8882"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_34_ab_en", "question": "Ward Hunt took which position from 1872 to 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_35_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of William Paterson from 1793 to 1806?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_36_ab_en", "question": "What position did Willis Van Devanter take from 1910 to 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_37_ab_en", "question": "Which position did David Souter hold from 1990 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_38_ab_en", "question": "What position did Abe Fortas take between 1965 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_39_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Thomas Campbell Clark hold between 1949 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_40_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of Joseph Story from 1812 to 1845?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_41_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Edward Douglass White hold from 1894 to 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_42_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Romano Prodi hold from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "President of the European Commission", "id": "Q8882"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_43_ab_en", "question": "Sonia Sotomayor took which position from 2009 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_44_ab_en", "question": "Stanley Forman Reed took which position between 1938 and 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_45_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Charles Evans Hughes hold between 1910 and 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_46_ab_en", "question": "William Johnson took which position between 1804 and 1834?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_47_ab_en", "question": "What position did Samuel Blatchford take between 1882 and 1893?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_48_ab_en", "question": "Mike Rogers took which position from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Federal Bureau of Investigation", "id": "Q8333"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_49_ab_en", "question": "Which position did William Henry Moody hold between 1906 and 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_50_ab_en", "question": "What position did Horace Gray take from 1881 to 1902?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_51_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of John Hessin Clarke between 1916 and 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_52_ab_en", "question": "What was the position of Sicco Mansholt from 1972 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "President of the European Commission", "id": "Q8882"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_53_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Brett Kavanaugh hold between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_54_ab_en", "question": "What position did Samuel Alito take from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_55_ab_en", "question": "Which position did Jean Rey hold from 1967 to 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "President of the European Commission", "id": "Q8882"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_56_ab_en", "question": "What position did Howell Edmunds Jackson take from 1893 to 1895?", "answer": [{"label": "Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States", "id": "Q11144"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_57_ab_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Flemming Lentfer in the year of 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of the Dannebrog", "id": "Q20872"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_58_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Hubert Lynes receive in the year of 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of Leopold", "id": "Q26126"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_59_ab_en", "question": "Markkleeberg received which award in the year of 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Fairtrade Town", "id": "Q44136"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_60_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Ainring receive in the year of 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Fairtrade Town", "id": "Q44136"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_61_ab_en", "question": "What award was endowed to An Unbelievable Story of Rape in 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Pulitzer Prize", "id": "Q46525"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_62_ab_en", "question": "Semyon Kosberg received which award in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "Lenin Prize", "id": "Q51067"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_63_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Alexander III of Russia receive in the year of 1866?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of the Southern Cross", "id": "Q93713"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_64_ab_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Frederick II of Prussia in the year of 1740?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of the Black Eagle", "id": "Q94145"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_65_ab_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Arthur Balfour in 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of Merit", "id": "Q94056"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_66_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Bill Pickering receive in the year of 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "IEEE Fellow", "id": "Q111734"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_67_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Daizhan Cheng receive during 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "IEEE Fellow", "id": "Q111734"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_68_ab_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Rafael Hui in the year of 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Grand Bauhinia Medal", "id": "Q114985"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_69_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Graz receive during 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "European Capital of Culture", "id": "Q129372"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_70_ab_en", "question": "Athens received which award during 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "European Capital of Culture", "id": "Q129372"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_71_ab_en", "question": "Bonn Minster received which award in the year of 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "minor basilica", "id": "Q120560"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_72_ab_en", "question": "Rita Moreno received which award in the year of 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Library of Congress", "id": "Q131454"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_73_ab_en", "question": "Which award did Sherlock Holmes receive in 1894?", "answer": [{"label": "Legion of Honour", "id": "Q163700"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_74_ab_en", "question": "Ivan Selifonov received which award during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Hero of the Soviet Union", "id": "Q178473"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_75_ab_en", "question": "Henry VIII of England received which award during 1503?", "answer": [{"label": "Prince of Wales", "id": "Q180729"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_76_ab_en", "question": "Ivan Selifonov received which award in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of Lenin", "id": "Q185493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_77_ab_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Central Volga Krai during 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "Order of Lenin", "id": "Q185493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_78_ab_en", "question": "What was the name of the employer Rexford Tugwell work for between 1938 and 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_79_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Patricia Harris work for from 2002 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_80_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did John Celivergos Zachos work for from 1861 to 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_81_ab_en", "question": "George Forsythe was an employee for whom from 1945 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_82_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Cornelius Lanczos work for between 1946 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_83_ab_en", "question": "Who did Thomas Pynchon work for between 1960 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_84_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Robert Love work for from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_85_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Laurent Rossi work for from 2012 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_86_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Tianyi Geng work for between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_87_ab_en", "question": "Manu Cornet was an employee for whom between 2007 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_88_ab_en", "question": "What was the name of the employer David Weinberger work for between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_89_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Arnnon Geshuri work for from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_90_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Jarkko Oikarinen work for between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_91_ab_en", "question": "Who did Quoc Viet Le work for from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_92_ab_en", "question": "What was the name of the employer Ifeoma Ozoma work for during 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_93_ab_en", "question": "Which employer did Samy Bengio work for between 2007 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_94_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was West Yorkshire located between 1974 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_95_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Prince Edward Island belong to between 1873 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_96_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was East Midlands located from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_97_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Cleveland belong to between 1974 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_98_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was preserved county of Wales located between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Wales", "id": "Q25"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_99_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Humberside belong to between 1974 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_100_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Budapest located from 1989 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hungary", "id": "Q28"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_101_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did West Lothian belong to between 1997 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Scotland", "id": "Q22"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_102_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Newry and Mourne District Council located from 1973 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Northern Ireland", "id": "Q26"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_103_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Moray belong to between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Scotland", "id": "Q22"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_104_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was City of Edinburgh located from 1996 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Scotland", "id": "Q22"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_105_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Vale of Glamorgan located from 1996 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Wales", "id": "Q25"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_106_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did County Down belong to between 1921 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Northern Ireland", "id": "Q26"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_107_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Edinburgh belong to from 1707 to 1845?", "answer": [{"label": "Scotland", "id": "Q22"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_108_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was East Lothian located between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Scotland", "id": "Q22"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_109_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Wismar belong to between 1632 and 1803?", "answer": [{"label": "Sweden", "id": "Q34"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_110_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Rhode Island belong to between 1790 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_111_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Galicia belong to between 1931 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_112_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Alytus District Municipality located between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_113_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Kaunas District Municipality located between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_114_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Kaunas District Municipality belong to from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_115_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Jurbarkas District Municipality located between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_116_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Skuodas District Municipality located from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_117_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Kalisz Voivodeship located between 1989 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Poland", "id": "Q36"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_118_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Ignalina District Municipality located from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_119_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Vilnius District Municipality belong to from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_120_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Skuodas District Municipality belong to between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_121_ab_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Vilnius District Municipality belong to between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Lithuania", "id": "Q37"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_122_ab_en", "question": "Where was Alexander Neckam educated from 1170 to 1182?", "answer": [{"label": "Paris", "id": "Q90"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_123_ab_en", "question": "Where was Pierre de Villiers educated between 1973 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "Prytanée National Militaire", "id": "Q271"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_124_ab_en", "question": "Rodolphe Belmer went to which school between 1980 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "Prytanée National Militaire", "id": "Q271"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_125_ab_en", "question": "Which school did Pierre Schill go to between 1984 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "Prytanée National Militaire", "id": "Q271"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_126_ab_en", "question": "Which school did Louis Rossel go to between 1855 and 1862?", "answer": [{"label": "Prytanée National Militaire", "id": "Q271"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_127_ab_en", "question": "Arnaud de La Grange went to which school between 1982 and 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "Prytanée National Militaire", "id": "Q271"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_128_ab_en", "question": "Where was Olivier de Germay educated from 1978 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "Prytanée National Militaire", "id": "Q271"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_129_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in TikTok between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "censorship", "id": "Q543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_130_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to TikTok from 2018 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "censorship", "id": "Q543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_131_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Germany between 1957 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Saarland", "id": "Q1201"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_132_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to NTT Docomo Yoyogi Building from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "clock", "id": "Q376"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_133_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in HMS Erebus between 1845 and 1848?", "answer": [{"label": "Franklin's lost expedition", "id": "Q2305"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_134_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Panathenaic Stadium in 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "2004 Summer Olympics", "id": "Q8558"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_135_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Vasily Lazarev from 1973 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_136_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Yusaku Maezawa in 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_137_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Mark Shuttleworth in 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_138_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Richard Garriott in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_139_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Mamoru Mohri in 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_140_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Mamoru Mohri during 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_141_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Klim Shipenko in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_142_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Dennis Tito in the year of 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_143_ab_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Yulia Peresild during 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "spaceflight", "id": "Q5916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_144_ab_en", "question": "Where did Caspar Schmalkalden work during 1648?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_145_ab_en", "question": "Where did Konstantin Somov work from 1923 to 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_146_ab_en", "question": "Theodor de Bry worked in  which location from 1580 to 1587?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_147_ab_en", "question": "Eva Zeisel worked in  which location from 1938 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_148_ab_en", "question": "What was the working location for George Soros from 1956 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_149_ab_en", "question": "What was the working location for Anders Zorn between 1893 and 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_150_ab_en", "question": "George Herriman worked in  which location between 1895 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_151_ab_en", "question": "What was the working location for Thomas Eakins between 1869 and 1870?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_152_ab_en", "question": "Where did Dominique Vivant work from 1808 to 1809?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_153_ab_en", "question": "Nikolai Sheremetev worked in  which location between 1769 and 1773?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_154_ab_en", "question": "What was the working location for Lee Miller between 1926 and 1929?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_155_ab_en", "question": "Where did Henry VII of England work from 1457 to 1471?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_156_ab_en", "question": "Where did Josep Maria Subirachs work between 1954 and 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "Belgium", "id": "Q31"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_157_ab_en", "question": "Where did Guillaume Apollinaire work between 1901 and 1902?", "answer": [{"label": "Belgium", "id": "Q31"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_158_ab_en", "question": "What was the working location for Paolo Troubetzkoy from 1914 to 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_159_ab_en", "question": "Who owned PZL Mielec between 1945 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Poland", "id": "Q36"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_160_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Ainola from 1972 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Finland", "id": "Q33"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_161_ab_en", "question": "Who owned The Great Masturbator between 1990 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_162_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Mount Vernon between 1754 and 1799?", "answer": [{"label": "George Washington", "id": "Q23"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_163_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Saint George between 1856 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Italy", "id": "Q38"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_164_ab_en", "question": "The Tempest was owned by whom from 1856 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Italy", "id": "Q38"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_165_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Hotel Bellevue Palace between 1994 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Switzerland", "id": "Q39"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_166_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Palais Wilson from 1936 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "Switzerland", "id": "Q39"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_167_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Bank of England between 1946 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United Kingdom", "id": "Q145"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_168_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Dante and Virgil in Hell between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "France", "id": "Q142"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_169_ab_en", "question": "Who owned The Magpie from 1984 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "France", "id": "Q142"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_170_ab_en", "question": "Palau became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_171_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Yemen join in the year of 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_172_ab_en", "question": "Turkmenistan became a member of what organization or association in 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_173_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Pakistan join in the year of 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_174_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Kiribati join in 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_175_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Afghanistan join during 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_176_ab_en", "question": "Philippines became a member of what organization or association in 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_177_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Tuvalu join in the year of 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_178_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Ecuador join during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_179_ab_en", "question": "Honduras became a member of what organization or association in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_180_ab_en", "question": "Bolivia became a member of what organization or association in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_181_ab_en", "question": "Colombia became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_182_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Indonesia join during 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_183_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Nauru join in the year of 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_184_ab_en", "question": "What organization did The Gambia join during 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_185_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Singapore join in the year of 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_186_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Grenada join in 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_187_ab_en", "question": "What organization did East Timor join during 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_188_ab_en", "question": "Belize became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_189_ab_en", "question": "Senegal became a member of what organization or association during 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_190_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Cyprus join in the year of 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_191_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Commonwealth of the Philippines join in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_192_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Republic of Ireland join in 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_193_ab_en", "question": "Albania became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_194_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Czech Republic join in 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_195_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Kingdom of Burundi join in 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_196_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Monaco join in the year of 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_197_ab_en", "question": "What organization did United States of America join in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_198_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Turkey join in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_199_ab_en", "question": "Uzbekistan became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_200_ab_en", "question": "Australia became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_201_ab_en", "question": "Iraq became a member of what organization or association during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_202_ab_en", "question": "Guatemala became a member of what organization or association during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_203_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Dominican Republic join during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_204_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Ethiopia join in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_205_ab_en", "question": "Iceland became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_206_ab_en", "question": "What organization did North Macedonia join during 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_207_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Ukraine join during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_208_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Bahrain join in 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_209_ab_en", "question": "What organization did United Arab Emirates join in 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_210_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Kenya join in 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_211_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Angola join during 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_212_ab_en", "question": "Sierra Leone became a member of what organization or association during 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_213_ab_en", "question": "Mali became a member of what organization or association in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_214_ab_en", "question": "Vanuatu became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_215_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Sudan join during 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_216_ab_en", "question": "Republic of China became a member of what organization or association during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_217_ab_en", "question": "Laos became a member of what organization or association during 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_218_ab_en", "question": "Israel became a member of what organization or association in 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_219_ab_en", "question": "Russia became a member of what organization or association during 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_220_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Latvia join in the year of 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_221_ab_en", "question": "Croatia became a member of what organization or association in 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_222_ab_en", "question": "Slovakia became a member of what organization or association during 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_223_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Tajikistan join in the year of 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_224_ab_en", "question": "Chile became a member of what organization or association during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_225_ab_en", "question": "Federation of Malaya became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_226_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Thailand join in 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_227_ab_en", "question": "Cuba became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_228_ab_en", "question": "Germany became a member of what organization or association in 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_229_ab_en", "question": "Malta became a member of what organization or association in 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_230_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Montenegro join during 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_231_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Portugal join during 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_232_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Central African Empire join during 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_233_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Indonesia join during 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_234_ab_en", "question": "United Arab Republic became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_235_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Belgium join during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_236_ab_en", "question": "Brazil became a member of what organization or association in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_237_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Central African Republic join in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_238_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Mauritius join during 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_239_ab_en", "question": "Uganda became a member of what organization or association in 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_240_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Algeria join in 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_241_ab_en", "question": "Guyana became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_242_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Fiji join in the year of 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_243_ab_en", "question": "What organization did South Africa join in the year of 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_244_ab_en", "question": "Guinea became a member of what organization or association during 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_245_ab_en", "question": "Central African Republic became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_246_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Rwanda join in the year of 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_247_ab_en", "question": "Papua New Guinea became a member of what organization or association during 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_248_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Tunisia join in 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_249_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Commonwealth realm of Guyana join in the year of 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_250_ab_en", "question": "Nigeria became a member of what organization or association in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_251_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Niger join in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_252_ab_en", "question": "What organization did Antigua and Barbuda join in the year of 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_253_ab_en", "question": "Federated States of Micronesia became a member of what organization or association in 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_254_ab_en", "question": "New Zealand became a member of what organization or association in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_255_ab_en", "question": "What organization did India join during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_256_ab_en", "question": "Venezuela became a member of what organization or association during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations", "id": "Q1065"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_257_ab_en", "question": "Republic of Ireland became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_258_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of European Union from 1973 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Republic of Ireland", "id": "Q27"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_259_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of European Union between 1986 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_260_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Organization of Turkic States between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hungary", "id": "Q28"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_261_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Schengen Area between 1995 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_262_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Council of Europe between 1977 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_263_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of NATO between 1982 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_264_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Schengen Area from 2001 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Norway", "id": "Q20"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_265_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of NATO between 1949 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Norway", "id": "Q20"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_266_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Council of Europe from 1949 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Republic of Ireland", "id": "Q27"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_267_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Allies of the First World War from 1917 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_268_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Community of Portuguese Language Countries from 1996 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Portugal", "id": "Q45"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_269_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Commonwealth of Independent States from 1991 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Ukraine", "id": "Q212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_270_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Collective Security Treaty Organization from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Georgia", "id": "Q230"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_271_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Eurasian Customs Union between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kazakhstan", "id": "Q232"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_272_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Eurasian Economic Union between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kazakhstan", "id": "Q232"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_273_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Commonwealth of Independent States between 1993 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Georgia", "id": "Q230"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_274_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Stabilisation and Association Agreement between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Montenegro", "id": "Q236"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_275_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Alliance for Open Media from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Intel", "id": "Q248"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_276_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of British Windward Islands between 1833 and 1885?", "answer": [{"label": "Barbados", "id": "Q244"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_277_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries from 1969 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Algeria", "id": "Q262"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_278_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of ASEAN between 1967 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Indonesia", "id": "Q252"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_279_ab_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Organization of Turkic States between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Uzbekistan", "id": "Q265"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_280_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Annapolis Royal belong to between 1867 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_281_ab_en", "question": "Which country did BritBox belong to between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_282_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Vision Eternel belong to between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_283_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Eurocorps belong to from 2003 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_284_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Urup belong to from 1875 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_285_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Broutona belong to between 1875 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_286_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Kurilsk belong to between 1855 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_287_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Simushir belong to between 1875 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_288_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Kunashir Island belong to from 1945 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_289_ab_en", "question": "Which country did Sakhalin belong to between 1917 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_290_ab_en", "question": "Which ethical group did Balthazar belong to from 1400 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Black people", "id": "Q817393"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_291_ab_en", "question": "Which political party did Ilya Ponomarev belong to between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Green Alliance–The People's Party", "id": "Q3173"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_292_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Jerzy Buzek a member of from 1980 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Solidarity", "id": "Q1003"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_293_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Oleksandr Vilkul a member of from 2005 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_294_ab_en", "question": "Which political party did Viktor Yanukovych belong to from 2000 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_295_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Konstantin Pavlov a member of from 2005 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_296_ab_en", "question": "Which political party did Anatoliy Fedorchuk belong to between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_297_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Valentin Demidov a member of from 2005 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_298_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Olga Kovitidi a member of from 2010 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_299_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Yuriy Boyko a member of from 2007 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Party of Regions", "id": "Q4266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_300_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Wilhelm Kopf a member of between 1938 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nazi Party", "id": "Q7320"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_301_ab_en", "question": "Which party was Hans Weisbach a member of from 1937 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nazi Party", "id": "Q7320"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_302_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Seoul between 2011 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Park Won-soon", "id": "Q22803"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_303_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Australia from 1923 to 1929?", "answer": [{"label": "Stanley Bruce", "id": "Q23358"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_304_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Benin between 2011 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Pascal Koupaki", "id": "Q29035"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_305_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Hong Kong between 2017 and 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Carrie Lam", "id": "Q19217"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_306_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Austria between 1961 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "Alfons Gorbach", "id": "Q29008"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_307_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Sofia in 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Todor Zhivkov", "id": "Q28517"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_308_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United States of America from 1901 to 1909?", "answer": [{"label": "Theodore Roosevelt", "id": "Q33866"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_309_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Australia between 1901 and 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "Edmund Barton", "id": "Q23342"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_310_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of First Hatta Cabinet between 1948 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Mohammad Hatta", "id": "Q29050"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_311_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Taipei between 1998 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Ma Ying-jeou", "id": "Q19216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_312_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Taipei between 1994 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Chen Shui-bian", "id": "Q22368"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_313_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Kyiv between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vitali Klitschko", "id": "Q31919"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_314_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Montana between 2013 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Steve Bullock", "id": "Q24015"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_315_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Andorra between 2011 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Antoni Martí", "id": "Q24801"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_316_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Helsinki between 2017 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Jan Vapaavuori", "id": "Q32219"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_317_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Wales from 1999 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Alun Michael", "id": "Q19397"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_318_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Russia from 2012 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Dmitry Medvedev", "id": "Q23530"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_319_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Czech Republic between 2002 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimír Špidla", "id": "Q32777"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_320_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Taipei City Government from 1998 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Ma Ying-jeou", "id": "Q19216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_321_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Czech Republic between 1998 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Miloš Zeman", "id": "Q29032"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_322_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Taipei City Government from 1994 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Chen Shui-bian", "id": "Q22368"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_323_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Russia between 1991 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "Boris Yeltsin", "id": "Q34453"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_324_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United States of America from 1881 to 1885?", "answer": [{"label": "Chester A. Arthur", "id": "Q35498"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_325_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Odesa Oblast from 2015 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Mikheil Saakashvili", "id": "Q43330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_326_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic between 1944 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "Nikita Khrushchev", "id": "Q35314"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_327_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Poland between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Donald Tusk", "id": "Q946"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_328_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Germany between 2005 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Angela Merkel", "id": "Q567"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_329_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Canada between 2006 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Harper", "id": "Q206"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_330_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of India between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Narendra Modi", "id": "Q1058"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_331_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Dominion of India between 1947 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "Jawaharlal Nehru", "id": "Q1047"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_332_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Germany between 1949 and 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "Konrad Adenauer", "id": "Q2492"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_333_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United Kingdom between 2010 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "David Cameron", "id": "Q192"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_334_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Russian Soviet Federative Socialist Republic between 1922 and 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir Lenin", "id": "Q1394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_335_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of India from 1966 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "Indira Gandhi", "id": "Q1149"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_336_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Poland from 2007 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Donald Tusk", "id": "Q946"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_337_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Italy from 1979 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "Francesco Cossiga", "id": "Q1230"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_338_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Russian Socialist Federative Soviet Republic from 1917 to 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir Lenin", "id": "Q1394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_339_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Italy during 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Giovanni Leone", "id": "Q1235"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_340_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Berlin from 1957 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "Willy Brandt", "id": "Q2514"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_341_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Second Merkel cabinet from 2009 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Angela Merkel", "id": "Q567"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_342_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Third Cabinet of Donald Tusk between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Donald Tusk", "id": "Q946"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_343_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Paris from 1977 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Jacques Chirac", "id": "Q2105"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_344_ab_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Turkey between 2002 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Abdullah Gül", "id": "Q42852"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_345_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Lara Fabian between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_346_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Kenny Omega hold from 1983 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_347_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Dennis Kwok hold between 1978 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_348_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Alex Trebek hold between 1940 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_349_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Shenae Grimes between 1989 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_350_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Victor Li between 1983 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_351_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Alvin Yeung hold from 1998 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_352_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Rafael Bienvenido Cruz hold between 1968 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_353_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Nellie Chin Yu from 1976 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_354_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Liu Qikun hold between 1988 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_355_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Evgeny Bareev between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_356_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Tom Green between 1971 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_357_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Aliocha Schneider hold from 1993 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_358_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Anastasia Lin hold from 2003 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_359_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Ted Cruz hold between 1970 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_360_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Patty Tsai between 1993 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_361_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Eddie Peng hold from 1995 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_362_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Jasmin Glaesser hold from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_363_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Richard Lee Armstrong from 1979 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_364_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Frank Stallone hold between 1919 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_365_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Li Hak Kan hold between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_366_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Mike Schreiner from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_367_ab_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Lauren Holly between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_368_ab_en", "question": "What citizenship did Nina Dobrev hold from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_369_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Air Liquide between 2006 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Benoît Potier", "id": "Q3622"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_370_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Free Democratic Party from 1948 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Theodor Heuss", "id": "Q2594"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_371_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Social Democratic Party of Germany between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Gerhard Schröder", "id": "Q2530"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_372_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of German Bundestag from 1976 to 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "Karl Carstens", "id": "Q2569"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_373_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Federal Ministry of Justice between 1966 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "Gustav Heinemann", "id": "Q2573"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_374_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Free Software Foundation from 1985 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard Stallman", "id": "Q7439"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_375_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of European Film Academy from 1989 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Ingmar Bergman", "id": "Q7546"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_376_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Christian Democratic Union from 1973 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Helmut Kohl", "id": "Q2518"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_377_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of European Bank for Reconstruction and Development between 1998 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Horst Köhler", "id": "Q2542"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_378_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Ministry of Finance from 1972 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Helmut Schmidt", "id": "Q2516"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_379_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of La France Insoumise group between 2017 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jean-Luc Mélenchon", "id": "Q5829"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_380_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Ministry for Economic Cooperation and Development between 1961 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "Walter Scheel", "id": "Q2571"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_381_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of National Rally between 1972 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Jean-Marie Le Pen", "id": "Q7177"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_382_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United Russia between 2008 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir Putin", "id": "Q7747"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_383_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of British Science Association from 1967 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Kathleen Lonsdale", "id": "Q7513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_384_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Democratic Convergence of Catalonia from 2012 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Artur Mas", "id": "Q8015"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_385_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Federal Ministry of Defence of Germany from 1969 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "Helmut Schmidt", "id": "Q2516"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_386_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Chinese Communist Party from 1945 to 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "Mao Zedong", "id": "Q5816"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_387_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Free Democratic Party from 1968 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Walter Scheel", "id": "Q2571"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_388_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of FDP Bundestag fraction in the year of 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Theodor Heuss", "id": "Q2594"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_389_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Foreign Office from 1966 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "Willy Brandt", "id": "Q2514"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_390_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Law and Justice between 2001 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Lech Kaczyński", "id": "Q2757"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_391_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United States Department of State from 2009 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Hillary Clinton", "id": "Q6294"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_392_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Olympique Lyonnais between 1987 and 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Jean-Michel Aulas", "id": "Q4245"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_393_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Wikimedia Foundation from 2012 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Kat Walsh", "id": "Q7545"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_394_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Chancellery between 1968 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "Karl Carstens", "id": "Q2569"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_395_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Social Democratic Party of Germany between 1964 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "Willy Brandt", "id": "Q2514"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_396_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Cabinet of Joe Biden from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Joe Biden", "id": "Q6279"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_397_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Economic Community of West African States from 2017 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Faure Essozimna Gnassingbé", "id": "Q4414"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_398_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Max Planck Society between 1960 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "Adolf Butenandt", "id": "Q5327"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_399_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Foreign Office in the year of 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "Helmut Schmidt", "id": "Q2516"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_400_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of UEFA from 2007 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Michel Platini", "id": "Q4261"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_401_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of RUSADA from 2016 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Yelena Isinbayeva", "id": "Q6319"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_402_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Convergence and Union between 2003 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Artur Mas", "id": "Q8015"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_403_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Christian Democratic Union between 1967 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Kurt Georg Kiesinger", "id": "Q2512"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_404_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Federal Ministry for Economic Affairs and Climate Action in the year of 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "Helmut Schmidt", "id": "Q2516"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_405_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of SPD Berlin from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "Willy Brandt", "id": "Q2514"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_406_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Social Democrats from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Mette Frederiksen", "id": "Q5015"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_407_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of CDU Berlin between 1981 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard von Weizsäcker", "id": "Q2567"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_408_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology from 1978 to 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "Mildred Cohn", "id": "Q7465"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_409_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Independent Republicans from 1966 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Valéry Giscard d'Estaing", "id": "Q2124"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_410_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of World Athletics between 1999 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Lamine Diack", "id": "Q1639"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_411_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Russian Social Democratic Labour Party from 1903 to 1905?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir Lenin", "id": "Q1394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_412_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Union for a Popular Movement between 2004 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Nicolas Sarkozy", "id": "Q329"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_413_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Committee on Foreign Affairs between 1954 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "Kurt Georg Kiesinger", "id": "Q2512"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_414_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Canadian Alliance from 2002 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Harper", "id": "Q206"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_415_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Bank of Italy between 1979 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "Carlo Azeglio Ciampi", "id": "Q1224"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_416_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of World Athletics between 1912 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Sigfrid Edström", "id": "Q1625"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_417_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Conservative Party of Canada from 2004 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Harper", "id": "Q206"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_418_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of International Olympic Committee between 1942 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Sigfrid Edström", "id": "Q1625"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_419_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Union for a Popular Movement from 2014 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Nicolas Sarkozy", "id": "Q329"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_420_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of The Republicans from 2015 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Nicolas Sarkozy", "id": "Q329"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_421_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of International Olympic Committee from 1946 to 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "Sigfrid Edström", "id": "Q1625"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_422_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights from 2018 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Michelle Bachelet", "id": "Q320"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_423_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of European Movement International between 1989 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Valéry Giscard d'Estaing", "id": "Q2124"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_424_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head of Wikimedia Foundation from 2003 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Jimmy Wales", "id": "Q181"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_425_ab_en", "question": "European Atomic Energy Community was a part of what between 1967 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_426_ab_en", "question": "Finland was a part of what from 1995 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_427_ab_en", "question": "Romania was a part of what from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_428_ab_en", "question": "European Coal and Steel Community was a part of what from 1967 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_429_ab_en", "question": "Poland was a part of what from 2004 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_430_ab_en", "question": "United Kingdom was a part of what between 1973 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "European Union", "id": "Q458"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_431_ab_en", "question": "Sylhet Region was a part of what between 1947 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Pakistan", "id": "Q843"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_432_ab_en", "question": "Pierrefonds was a part of what from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Montreal", "id": "Q340"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_433_ab_en", "question": "Sylhet Region was a part of what between 1947 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "India", "id": "Q668"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_434_ab_en", "question": "Gabu was a part of what between 1973 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Guinea-Bissau", "id": "Q1007"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_435_ab_en", "question": "Golm was a part of what between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Potsdam", "id": "Q1711"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_436_ab_en", "question": "Klein Glienicke was a part of what from 1939 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Potsdam", "id": "Q1711"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_437_ab_en", "question": "High Speed Photometer was a part of what between 1990 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_438_ab_en", "question": "Cosmic Origins Spectrograph was a part of what between 2009 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_439_ab_en", "question": "Faint Object Camera was a part of what between 1990 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_440_ab_en", "question": "Wide Field and Planetary Camera was a part of what between 1990 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_441_ab_en", "question": "Corrective Optics Space Telescope Axial Replacement was a part of what between 1993 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_442_ab_en", "question": "Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph was a part of what between 1997 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_443_ab_en", "question": "Goddard High Resolution Spectrograph was a part of what between 1990 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_444_ab_en", "question": "Faint Object Spectrograph was a part of what from 1990 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_445_ab_en", "question": "Advanced Camera for Surveys was a part of what from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hubble Space Telescope", "id": "Q2513"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_446_ab_en", "question": "Maine was a part of what from 1652 to 1820?", "answer": [{"label": "Massachusetts", "id": "Q771"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_447_ab_en", "question": "European Union Civil Service Tribunal was a part of what from 2005 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Court of Justice of the European Union", "id": "Q4951"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_448_ab_en", "question": "Where did Thomas Romain live from 2003 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_449_ab_en", "question": "What was the residence of Michael Redmond from 1976 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_450_ab_en", "question": "Where did Christabel Pankhurst live from 1921 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_451_ab_en", "question": "Where did Ferenc Rofusz live from 1988 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_452_ab_en", "question": "What was the residence of Rahaf Mohammed between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_453_ab_en", "question": "What was the residence of Wolf Koenig between 1937 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_454_ab_en", "question": "Where did Alexandre Alexeieff live between 1943 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_455_ab_en", "question": "Where did Maurice Ascalon live from 1913 to 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "Hungary", "id": "Q28"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_456_ab_en", "question": "Where did Ferenc Rofusz live from 1946 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "Hungary", "id": "Q28"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_457_ab_en", "question": "What operated Orbiter Processing Facility from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_458_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of astronaut transfer van from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_459_ab_en", "question": "What operated Embassy of Turkey in Austria from 1916 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Turkey", "id": "Q43"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_460_ab_en", "question": "What operated reCAPTCHA between 2009 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_461_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of Wikipedia between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Wikimedia Foundation", "id": "Q180"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_462_ab_en", "question": "What operated Fort Barry between 1908 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_463_ab_en", "question": "What operated Fort Washington Park from 1809 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_464_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of Fort Tilden from 1917 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_465_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of Molli railway between 1994 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Deutsche Bahn", "id": "Q9322"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_466_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of Anfield between 1884 and 1892?", "answer": [{"label": "Everton F.C.", "id": "Q5794"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_467_ab_en", "question": "What operated Brooks Air Force Base between 1917 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_468_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of MOD St Athan from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cardiff Airport", "id": "Q8994"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_469_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of Robert Schumann Hochschule between 1973 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "North Rhine-Westphalia", "id": "Q1198"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_470_ab_en", "question": "What was the operator of USS Foote from 1919 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Navy", "id": "Q11220"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_471_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Saint Petersburg between 1990 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_472_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Amman from 1988 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cairo", "id": "Q85"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_473_ab_en", "question": "Bordeaux was twinned with which city between 1964 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_474_ab_en", "question": "Salzburg was twinned with which city from 2007 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Bern", "id": "Q70"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_475_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Miami Beach from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Basel", "id": "Q78"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_476_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Delhi from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_477_ab_en", "question": "Nagoya was twinned with which city between 1959 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_478_ab_en", "question": "Berlin was twinned with which city from 1967 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_479_ab_en", "question": "New York City was twinned with which city from 1982 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cairo", "id": "Q85"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_480_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tbilisi between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cairo", "id": "Q85"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_481_ab_en", "question": "Beijing was twinned with which city from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_482_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Taipei from 1979 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_483_ab_en", "question": "Amman was twinned with which city between 2005 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Geneva", "id": "Q71"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_484_ab_en", "question": "Zagreb was twinned with which city from 2009 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_485_ab_en", "question": "Tokyo was twinned with which city between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_486_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Moscow from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_487_ab_en", "question": "New York City was twinned with which city between 2001 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_488_ab_en", "question": "Auckland was twinned with which city from 1971 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_489_ab_en", "question": "Mexico City was twinned with which city between 1969 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_490_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Berlin from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_491_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of San Francisco between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Zürich", "id": "Q72"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_492_ab_en", "question": "Lusaka was twinned with which city from 1968 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_493_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Yerevan from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_494_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Cotonou between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Geneva", "id": "Q71"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_495_ab_en", "question": "Rio de Janeiro was twinned with which city between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_496_ab_en", "question": "Vinnytsia was twinned with which city from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Zürich", "id": "Q72"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_497_ab_en", "question": "Los Angeles was twinned with which city between 1967 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_498_ab_en", "question": "Eilat was twinned with which city between 1959 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_499_ab_en", "question": "Shanghai was twinned with which city between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "London", "id": "Q84"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_500_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Kunming between 1982 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Zürich", "id": "Q72"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_501_ab_en", "question": "Tehran was twinned with which city from 1972 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Los Angeles", "id": "Q65"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_502_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Shanghai from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Basel", "id": "Q78"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_503_ab_en", "question": "City of Brussels was twinned with which city from 1992 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_504_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Aalborg Municipality between 1979 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_505_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tokyo from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_506_ab_en", "question": "Leiria was twinned with which city from 1996 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_507_ab_en", "question": "Milan was twinned with which city between 1961 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_508_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Buenos Aires from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_509_ab_en", "question": "Beijing was twinned with which city from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_510_ab_en", "question": "Erfurt was twinned with which city from 1972 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_511_ab_en", "question": "Montevideo was twinned with which city from 2001 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_512_ab_en", "question": "Tbilisi was twinned with which city from 2009 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_513_ab_en", "question": "Santiago was twinned with which city between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_514_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Riga from 2005 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_515_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Huaibei from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_516_ab_en", "question": "Havana was twinned with which city between 1997 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_517_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Kyoto Prefecture between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Quebec", "id": "Q176"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_518_ab_en", "question": "Milan was twinned with which city from 2003 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Toronto", "id": "Q172"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_519_ab_en", "question": "Luanda was twinned with which city between 1993 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_520_ab_en", "question": "La Paz was twinned with which city between 1999 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_521_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Bamako between 2000 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_522_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Damascus from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_523_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Yerevan from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_524_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Toyama Prefecture between 1985 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q175"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_525_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Saint Petersburg between 2006 and 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_526_ab_en", "question": "Salzburg was twinned with which city between 1989 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_527_ab_en", "question": "Toronto was twinned with which city from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_528_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Duisburg between 1985 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_529_ab_en", "question": "Oslo was twinned with which city between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_530_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Santiago de Compostela between 2000 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_531_ab_en", "question": "Macau was twinned with which city between 2000 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_532_ab_en", "question": "Tokushima Prefecture was twinned with which city from 1984 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q175"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_533_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Chicago between 1993 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_534_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Madison from 1989 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_535_ab_en", "question": "Osaka was twinned with which city between 1985 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_536_ab_en", "question": "Mendoza was twinned with which city between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_537_ab_en", "question": "Bila Tserkva was twinned with which city between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_538_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Funchal from 1998 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_539_ab_en", "question": "Dnipro was twinned with which city between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_540_ab_en", "question": "Lisbon was twinned with which city between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_541_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tel Aviv between 2004 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_542_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Seoul between 1977 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_543_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Almaty between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_544_ab_en", "question": "Mie Prefecture was twinned with which city from 1973 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q175"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_545_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Coimbra between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_546_ab_en", "question": "Guangzhou was twinned with which city from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_547_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Naha from 1998 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_548_ab_en", "question": "Abidjan was twinned with which city from 1981 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "São Paulo", "id": "Q174"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_549_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Budapest between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_550_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Donetsk from 1996 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_551_ab_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tallinn between 1993 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_552_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Pavel Shuvalov have between 1895 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_553_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Andrei Grechko have between 1936 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_554_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Captain Nazi have between 2000 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_555_ab_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Pierre Henri Hugoniot from 1884 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_556_ab_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Rumen Radev from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_557_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Alexander Yefimov have from 1944 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_558_ab_en", "question": "What was the military rank of David Dragunsky between 1941 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_559_ab_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Sergey Denisov from 1937 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_560_ab_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Vladimir Ilyushin between 1953 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_561_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Alexander Molodchy have between 1942 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_562_ab_en", "question": "What was the military rank of August von Werder between 1846 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_563_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Vladimir Arsenyev have between 1912 and 1913?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_564_ab_en", "question": "What military rank did Alexander III of Russia have from 1862 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "captain", "id": "Q19100"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_565_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Heather Mills from 2002 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Paul McCartney", "id": "Q2599"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_566_ab_en", "question": "Who was Maureen Starkey Tigrett 's spouse from 1965 to 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "Ringo Starr", "id": "Q2632"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_567_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Hildegard of Vinzgouw between 772 and 783?", "answer": [{"label": "Charlemagne", "id": "Q3044"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_568_ab_en", "question": "Who was Freddie Stroma 's spouse from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Johanna Braddy", "id": "Q2597"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_569_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Christina Hendricks between 2009 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Geoffrey Arend", "id": "Q3195"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_570_ab_en", "question": "Who was Linda McCartney 's spouse between 1969 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Paul McCartney", "id": "Q2599"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_571_ab_en", "question": "Who was Emma Heming Willis 's spouse from 2009 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bruce Willis", "id": "Q2680"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_572_ab_en", "question": "Who was Desiderata of the Lombards 's spouse between 770 and 771?", "answer": [{"label": "Charlemagne", "id": "Q3044"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_573_ab_en", "question": "Who was Carrie Fisher 's spouse from 1983 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "Paul Simon", "id": "Q4028"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_574_ab_en", "question": "Who was Fastrada 's spouse between 784 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charlemagne", "id": "Q3044"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_575_ab_en", "question": "Who was Fastrada 's spouse from 783 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charlemagne", "id": "Q3044"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_576_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Lisa Marie Presley from 1994 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Michael Jackson", "id": "Q2831"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_577_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Barbara Bach between 1981 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ringo Starr", "id": "Q2632"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_578_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Hildegard of Vinzgouw between 771 and 783?", "answer": [{"label": "Charlemagne", "id": "Q3044"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_579_ab_en", "question": "Who was Josh Blaylock 's spouse from 2012 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Johanna Braddy", "id": "Q2597"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_580_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of David Furnish between 2005 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Elton John", "id": "Q2808"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_581_ab_en", "question": "Who was Maria Shriver 's spouse between 1986 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Arnold Schwarzenegger", "id": "Q2685"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_582_ab_en", "question": "Who was Carrie Fisher 's spouse from 1983 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "Paul Simon", "id": "Q4028"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_583_ab_en", "question": "Who was Casimir Dudevant 's spouse from 1822 to 1835?", "answer": [{"label": "George Sand", "id": "Q3816"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_584_ab_en", "question": "Who was Sonia Orwell 's spouse from 1949 to 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "George Orwell", "id": "Q3335"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_585_ab_en", "question": "Who was Daniella Pick 's spouse from 2018 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Quentin Tarantino", "id": "Q3772"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_586_ab_en", "question": "Who was Margot Honecker 's spouse from 1953 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Erich Honecker", "id": "Q2607"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_587_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Debbie Rowe from 1996 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Michael Jackson", "id": "Q2831"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_588_ab_en", "question": "Who was Olivia Harrison 's spouse from 1978 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "George Harrison", "id": "Q2643"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_589_ab_en", "question": "Who was Claudia Schiffer 's spouse between 2002 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Matthew Vaughn", "id": "Q2593"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_590_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Edie Brickell from 1992 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Paul Simon", "id": "Q4028"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_591_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Pattie Boyd from 1966 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "George Harrison", "id": "Q2643"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_592_ab_en", "question": "Who was Queen Paola of Belgium 's spouse from 1959 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Albert II of Belgium", "id": "Q3911"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_593_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Demi Moore from 1987 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Bruce Willis", "id": "Q2680"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_594_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Galina Lukashenko from 1975 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Alexander Lukashenko", "id": "Q2866"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_595_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Princess Hermine Reuss of Greiz from 1922 to 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "Wilhelm II", "id": "Q2677"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_596_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Anna Magdalena Bach between 1721 and 1750?", "answer": [{"label": "Johann Sebastian Bach", "id": "Q1339"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_597_ab_en", "question": "Who was Julia Domna 's spouse between 187 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Septimius Severus", "id": "Q1442"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_598_ab_en", "question": "Who was David Thornton 's spouse between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cyndi Lauper", "id": "Q1545"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_599_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Maria Barbara Bach from 1707 to 1720?", "answer": [{"label": "Johann Sebastian Bach", "id": "Q1339"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_600_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Poppaea Sabina between 62 and 65?", "answer": [{"label": "Nero", "id": "Q1413"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_601_ab_en", "question": "Who was Fanny Stevenson 's spouse from 1880 to 1894?", "answer": [{"label": "Robert Louis Stevenson", "id": "Q1512"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_602_ab_en", "question": "Who was Fanny Stevenson 's spouse from 1880 to 1894?", "answer": [{"label": "Robert Louis Stevenson", "id": "Q1512"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_603_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Mirka Federer between 2009 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Roger Federer", "id": "Q1426"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_604_ab_en", "question": "Who was Claudia Octavia 's spouse from 53 to 62?", "answer": [{"label": "Nero", "id": "Q1413"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_605_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Nadezhda Krupskaya from 1898 to 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir Lenin", "id": "Q1394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_606_ab_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Cosima Wagner between 1870 and 1883?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard Wagner", "id": "Q1511"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_607_ab_en", "question": "Who was Statilia Messalina 's spouse between 66 and 68?", "answer": [{"label": "Nero", "id": "Q1413"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_608_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team South Korea national football team between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jürgen Klinsmann", "id": "Q57079"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_609_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Inter Milan between 2004 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Roberto Mancini", "id": "Q48330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_610_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Vissel Kobe between 2007 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Hiroshi Matsuda", "id": "Q47316"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_611_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team MSV Duisburg from 2013 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Karsten Baumann", "id": "Q49811"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_612_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team FC Zenit Saint Petersburg from 2017 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Roberto Mancini", "id": "Q48330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_613_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Austria national association football team from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ralf Rangnick", "id": "Q57902"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_614_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team CF Fuenlabrada from 2015 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Fernando Morientes", "id": "Q45567"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_615_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team FC Kariya between 2006 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Nariyasu Yasuhara", "id": "Q47363"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_616_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team VfL Wolfsburg between 2018 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Bruno Labbadia", "id": "Q57548"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_617_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Maria Sharapova between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jimmy Connors", "id": "Q53393"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_618_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team FC Erzgebirge Aue between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Marc Hensel", "id": "Q49783"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_619_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Inter Milan from 2014 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Roberto Mancini", "id": "Q48330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_620_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team PSV Eindhoven from 2022 to 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Ruud van Nistelrooy", "id": "Q45626"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_621_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Maria Sharapova from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jimmy Connors", "id": "Q53393"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_622_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team AC Milan from 2009 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Leonardo Araújo", "id": "Q46741"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_623_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team FC Erzgebirge Aue from 2012 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Karsten Baumann", "id": "Q49811"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_624_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team RB Leipzig between 2018 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Ralf Rangnick", "id": "Q57902"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_625_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team AS Monaco FC from 2018 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Thierry Henry", "id": "Q45901"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_626_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team OGC Nice between 2018 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Patrick Vieira", "id": "Q46347"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_627_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Vissel Kobe between 2005 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Pavel Řehák", "id": "Q47518"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_628_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Kei Nishikori from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Michael Chang", "id": "Q53370"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_629_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Saudi Arabia national football team from 2023 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Roberto Mancini", "id": "Q48330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_630_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Andy Roddick between 2006 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Jimmy Connors", "id": "Q53393"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_631_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart from 2010 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Bruno Labbadia", "id": "Q57548"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_632_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Andy Murray between 2008 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Àlex Corretja", "id": "Q46308"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_633_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Italy national association football team from 2018 to 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Roberto Mancini", "id": "Q48330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_634_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team RC Strasbourg between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Patrick Vieira", "id": "Q46347"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_635_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Hertha BSC from 2019 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Jürgen Klinsmann", "id": "Q57079"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_636_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team FC Bayern Munich between 2008 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Jürgen Klinsmann", "id": "Q57079"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_637_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team VfB Stuttgart II in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Andreas Hinkel", "id": "Q57217"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_638_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Hertha BSC between 2020 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Bruno Labbadia", "id": "Q57548"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_639_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Scotland national football team between 1985 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "Alex Ferguson", "id": "Q44980"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_640_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Juventus FC in the year of 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Angelo Alessio", "id": "Q62175"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_641_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Eintracht Frankfurt in the year of 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Jörg Berger", "id": "Q65482"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_642_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Qhubeka Assos between 2016 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Rolf Aldag", "id": "Q63242"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_643_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart from 2008 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Markus Babbel", "id": "Q61225"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_644_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team SK Sturm Graz between 2014 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Franco Foda", "id": "Q66080"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_645_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Eintracht Frankfurt between 1988 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Jörg Berger", "id": "Q65482"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_646_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Poland national association football team during 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Zbigniew Boniek", "id": "Q68039"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_647_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Austria national association football team from 2017 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Franco Foda", "id": "Q66080"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_648_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Tennis Borussia Berlin in the year of 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Mirko Slomka", "id": "Q61646"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_649_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Tennis Borussia Berlin from 2017 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Thomas Brdarić", "id": "Q62403"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_650_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Juventus FC between 2011 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonio Conte", "id": "Q26580"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_651_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Ukraine national association football team from 2016 to 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Andriy Shevchenko", "id": "Q41244"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_652_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Czech Republic national association football team in 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ivan Hašek", "id": "Q31376"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_653_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team AC Milan between 1975 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "Giovanni Trapattoni", "id": "Q44420"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_654_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Armenia national football team from 2006 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Ian Porterfield", "id": "Q28740"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_655_ab_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Clube de Regatas do Flamengo between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tite", "id": "Q40652"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_656_ab_en", "question": "Who coached the team Italy national association football team from 2014 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonio Conte", "id": "Q26580"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_657_ab_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Osei Bonsu from 1804 to 1824?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_658_ab_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Francesco II Sforza from 1521 to 1524?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_659_ab_en", "question": "What was Francesco II Sforza 's occupation between 1525 and 1535?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_660_ab_en", "question": "What was Reginfrid 's occupation from 812 to 814?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_661_ab_en", "question": "What was Idris Alooma 's occupation from 1580 to 1617?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_662_ab_en", "question": "What was Prempeh II 's occupation between 1931 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_663_ab_en", "question": "What was Naruhito 's occupation between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_664_ab_en", "question": "What was Harald Klak 's occupation between 812 and 813?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_665_ab_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Harald Klak between 819 and 823?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_666_ab_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Beatrix of the Netherlands between 1980 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_667_ab_en", "question": "What was Henry VIII of England 's occupation from 1509 to 1547?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_668_ab_en", "question": "What was Constantine II of Greece 's occupation between 1964 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_669_ab_en", "question": "What was Judith of Bavaria 's occupation from 819 to 840?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_670_ab_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Hemming of Denmark between 810 and 812?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_671_ab_en", "question": "What was Harald V of Norway 's occupation from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_672_ab_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Osei Tutu from 1680 to 1717?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_673_ab_en", "question": "What was William Herschel 's occupation between 1774 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "astronomer", "id": "Q11063"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_674_ab_en", "question": "What was Henri Joseph Anastase Perrotin 's occupation between 1873 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "astronomer", "id": "Q11063"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_675_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chief Executive of Hong Kong between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "CY Leung", "id": "Q15023"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_676_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of General Secretary of the Communist Party from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Xi Jinping", "id": "Q15031"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_677_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chairman of the Central Military Commission of the Chinese Communist Party from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Xi Jinping", "id": "Q15031"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_678_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Beijing between 2004 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Wang Qishan", "id": "Q18113"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_679_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Prime Minister of Belgium between 1918 and 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "Léon Delacroix", "id": "Q14989"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_680_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chief Executive of Hong Kong between 2017 and 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Carrie Lam", "id": "Q19217"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_681_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party between 1989 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Jiang Zemin", "id": "Q16597"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_682_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Prime Minister of Belgium from 1931 to 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "Jules Renkin", "id": "Q14995"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_683_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of Ukraine in 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Oleksandr Turchynov", "id": "Q15850"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_684_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party from 2002 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Hu Jintao", "id": "Q15029"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_685_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the Royal Astronomical Society between 1827 and 1829?", "answer": [{"label": "John Frederick William Herschel", "id": "Q14278"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_686_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Federal Minister of Finance from 2009 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Wolfgang Schäuble", "id": "Q16019"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_687_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chairman of the Central Military Commission of the Chinese Communist Party from 2004 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Hu Jintao", "id": "Q15029"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_688_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Grand Prince of Kiev between 978 and 1015?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir the Great", "id": "Q14974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_689_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the Royal Astronomical Society between 1839 and 1841?", "answer": [{"label": "John Frederick William Herschel", "id": "Q14278"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_690_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Leader of the Christian Democratic Union between 1998 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Wolfgang Schäuble", "id": "Q16019"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_691_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the European Commission from 2004 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "José Manuel Durão Barroso", "id": "Q15849"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_692_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Shanghai between 1988 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Zhu Rongji", "id": "Q18285"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_693_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Lucasian Professor of Mathematics from 1979 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Hawking", "id": "Q17714"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_694_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of member of the Politburo of the Chinese Communist Party from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Xi Jinping", "id": "Q15031"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_695_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of member of the Politburo of the Chinese Communist Party between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Li Keqiang", "id": "Q18111"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_696_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Shanghai between 1985 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "Jiang Zemin", "id": "Q16597"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_697_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Beijing from 2003 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Wang Qishan", "id": "Q18113"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_698_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the European Council between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Herman Van Rompuy", "id": "Q12983"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_699_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of Finland from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sauli Niinistö", "id": "Q29207"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_700_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of count of Holland between 1598 and 1621?", "answer": [{"label": "Philip III of Spain", "id": "Q34464"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_701_ab_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Secretary for Education between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Eddie Ng", "id": "Q19234"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_702_ab_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Fraunhofer Society from 1949 to 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "Walter Gerlach", "id": "Q61745"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_703_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Guards Corps from 1858 to 1878?", "answer": [{"label": "Prince August of Württemberg", "id": "Q64613"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_704_ab_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Max Planck Institute for Mathematics between 1980 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Friedrich Hirzebruch", "id": "Q61753"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_705_ab_en", "question": "Abwehr was managed or directed by whom from 1930 to 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "Ferdinand von Bredow", "id": "Q62632"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_706_ab_en", "question": "Who directed or managed CERN between 2009 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Rolf-Dieter Heuer", "id": "Q65092"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_707_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Koenigsberg Observatory from 1895 to 1904?", "answer": [{"label": "Hermann Struve", "id": "Q61836"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_708_ab_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Institute for Peace Research and Security Policy at the University of Hamburg from 1984 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Egon Bahr", "id": "Q62206"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_709_ab_en", "question": "European Southern Observatory was managed or directed by whom from 1962 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "Otto Heckmann", "id": "Q62016"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_710_ab_en", "question": "German General Staff was managed or directed by whom between 1888 and 1891?", "answer": [{"label": "Alfred von Waldersee", "id": "Q60680"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_711_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Egyptian Museum of Berlin from 1885 to 1914?", "answer": [{"label": "Adolf Erman", "id": "Q61421"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_712_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Seeberg Observatory between 1787 and 1806?", "answer": [{"label": "Franz Xaver von Zach", "id": "Q60662"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_713_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences from 1935 to 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard Courant", "id": "Q61046"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_714_ab_en", "question": "Jewish Museum Berlin was managed or directed by whom between 1997 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "W. Michael Blumenthal", "id": "Q62988"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_715_ab_en", "question": "Regensburger Domspatzen was managed or directed by whom from 1964 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Georg Ratzinger", "id": "Q61907"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_716_ab_en", "question": "Federal Intelligence Service was managed or directed by whom from 1956 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Reinhard Gehlen", "id": "Q57991"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_717_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Robert Koch Institute from 1913 to 1915?", "answer": [{"label": "Friedrich August Loeffler", "id": "Q60993"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_718_ab_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences from 1966 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "Kurt Otto Friedrichs", "id": "Q72978"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_719_ab_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Dachau concentration camp between 1933 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "Theodor Eicke", "id": "Q65098"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_720_ab_en", "question": "European Union shared border with what between 1957 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "Denmark", "id": "Q35"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_721_ab_en", "question": "What did European Union share border with between 1990 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Poland", "id": "Q36"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_722_ab_en", "question": "What did Czechoslovakia share border with from 1919 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "Austria", "id": "Q40"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_723_ab_en", "question": "Czechoslovakia shared border with what between 1918 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "Poland", "id": "Q36"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_724_ab_en", "question": "What did Yugoslavia share border with between 1929 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Italy", "id": "Q38"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_725_ab_en", "question": "What did Latvia share border with between 1918 and 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "Poland", "id": "Q36"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_726_ab_en", "question": "What did Arab League share border with from 1958 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_727_ab_en", "question": "What did Confederate States share border with between 1861 and 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_728_ab_en", "question": "What did Neutral Moresnet share border with from 1830 to 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "Belgium", "id": "Q31"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_729_ab_en", "question": "What did Arab League share border with between 1974 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kenya", "id": "Q114"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_730_ab_en", "question": "What did Turkey share border with from 1923 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Greece", "id": "Q41"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_731_ab_en", "question": "Estonia shared border with what from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Russia", "id": "Q159"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_732_ab_en", "question": "What did Latvia share border with from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Russia", "id": "Q159"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_733_ab_en", "question": "What did Turkey share border with between 1932 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Iraq", "id": "Q796"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_734_ab_en", "question": "Germany shared border with what between 1993 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Czech Republic", "id": "Q213"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_735_ab_en", "question": "Virginia shared border with what between 1796 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tennessee", "id": "Q1509"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_736_ab_en", "question": "Tajikistan shared border with what between 1885 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Afghanistan", "id": "Q889"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_737_ab_en", "question": "What did Virginia share border with from 1863 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "West Virginia", "id": "Q1371"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_738_ab_en", "question": "What did Estonia share border with between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Latvia", "id": "Q211"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_739_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Constantinople since in 330?", "answer": [{"label": "Byzantium", "id": "Q23725"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_740_ab_en", "question": "South Australia was replaced by what since during 1863?", "answer": [{"label": "New South Wales", "id": "Q3224"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_741_ab_en", "question": "South Australia was replaced by what since in the year of 1861?", "answer": [{"label": "New South Wales", "id": "Q3224"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_742_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Nazi Germany since in the year of 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "Weimar Republic", "id": "Q41304"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_743_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Landespolizei since in the year of 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Volkspolizei", "id": "Q56040"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_744_ab_en", "question": "German Democratic Republic was replaced by what since in the year of 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Soviet occupation zone of Germany", "id": "Q55300"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_745_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Viken since in the year of 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Buskerud", "id": "Q50618"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_746_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Viken since in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Østfold", "id": "Q50614"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_747_ab_en", "question": "canton of France was replaced by what since in 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "canton of France", "id": "Q184188"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_748_ab_en", "question": "Hombleux was replaced by what since in the year of 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Grécourt", "id": "Q156912"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_749_ab_en", "question": "universal time was replaced by what since in the year of 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "Greenwich Mean Time", "id": "Q30192"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_750_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Scottish council area since in the year of 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "local government area of Scotland 1975 to 1996", "id": "Q383493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_751_ab_en", "question": "Indonesia was replaced by what since during 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of Indonesia", "id": "Q523435"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_752_ab_en", "question": "Englon was replaced by what since during 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Shanghai Maple", "id": "Q391431"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_753_ab_en", "question": "Nazi Germany was replaced by what since in the year of 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "Federal State of Austria", "id": "Q176495"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_754_ab_en", "question": "Alfa Romeo Racing was replaced by what since in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Sauber", "id": "Q171335"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_755_ab_en", "question": "Scuderia AlphaTauri was replaced by what since in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Scuderia Toro Rosso", "id": "Q141818"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_756_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Porvoo since during 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Porvoo", "id": "Q193367"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_757_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Jordan since in the year of 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "Mandatory Palestine", "id": "Q193714"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_758_ab_en", "question": "International Community Radio Taipei was replaced by what since in the year of 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "American Forces Network", "id": "Q464570"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_759_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Avranches since in the year of 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Saint-Martin-des-Champs", "id": "Q581232"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_760_ab_en", "question": "Supreme Tribunal of Justice of Venezuela in exile was replaced by what since in 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Supreme Tribunal of Justice of Venezuela", "id": "Q578438"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_761_ab_en", "question": "Charleroi was replaced by what since in the year of 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "Roux", "id": "Q900429"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_762_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Viatris since in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Mylan", "id": "Q899010"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_763_ab_en", "question": "British Army of the Rhine was replaced by what since in the year of 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "21st Army Group", "id": "Q214026"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_764_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Northern Territory since during 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "South Australia", "id": "Q35715"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_765_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Gustave Eiffel University since in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Paris-Est Marne-la-Vallée", "id": "Q501207"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_766_ab_en", "question": "Dampierre was replaced by what since in the year of 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Le Petit-Mercey", "id": "Q769893"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_767_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Siikalatva since during 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Pulkkila", "id": "Q541236"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_768_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Sastamala since during 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Äetsä", "id": "Q252873"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_769_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Fontain since in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Arguel", "id": "Q651147"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_770_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Sastamala since during 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Mouhijärvi", "id": "Q661269"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_771_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Rouillac since during 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Rouillac", "id": "Q617937"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_772_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Khanate of Kokand since in 1822?", "answer": [{"label": "Senior juz", "id": "Q640998"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_773_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Nanchez since in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Villard-sur-Bienne", "id": "Q636792"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_774_ab_en", "question": "BBC News was replaced by what since in the year of 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "BBC World Service Television", "id": "Q639275"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_775_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Les Belleville since in the year of 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Saint-Jean-de-Belleville", "id": "Q747485"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_776_ab_en", "question": "Soviet Olympic Committee was replaced by what since in the year of 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "Estonian Olympic Committee", "id": "Q775081"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_777_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Charleroi since in the year of 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "Marcinelle", "id": "Q785440"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_778_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Common Booster Core from 1998 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_779_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Delta between 1997 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_780_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Mitsubishi Proudia between 2012 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Nissan Motor Co. Ltd.", "id": "Q20165"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_781_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Pentium D from 2005 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Intel", "id": "Q248"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_782_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Atlas II from 1995 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Lockheed Martin", "id": "Q7240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_783_ab_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Atlas IIAS between 1995 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Lockheed Martin", "id": "Q7240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_784_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Isuzu Gemini between 1993 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Honda", "id": "Q9584"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_785_ab_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Atlas IIA from 1995 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Lockheed Martin", "id": "Q7240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_786_ab_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Mitsubishi ASX from 2023 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Renault S.A.", "id": "Q6686"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_787_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Mitsubishi Dignity from 2012 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Nissan Motor Co. Ltd.", "id": "Q20165"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_788_ab_en", "question": "What manufactured Suzuki Landy from 2007 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Nissan Motor Co. Ltd.", "id": "Q20165"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_789_ab_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Nissan Livina between 2006 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Nissan Motor Co. Ltd.", "id": "Q20165"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_790_ab_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Nissan Livina from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Mitsubishi Motors", "id": "Q36033"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_791_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Rabat between 1956 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Morocco", "id": "Q1028"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_792_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Manila between 1976 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Philippines", "id": "Q928"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_793_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Zomba between 1880 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Malawi", "id": "Q1020"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_794_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Bujumbura between 1962 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Burundi", "id": "Q967"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_795_ab_en", "question": "Abuja was the capital of what between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nigeria", "id": "Q1033"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_796_ab_en", "question": "Manila was the capital of what between 1946 and 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "Philippines", "id": "Q928"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_797_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Brazzaville from 1958 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Republic of the Congo", "id": "Q971"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_798_ab_en", "question": "Taipei was the capital of what from 1949 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Taiwan", "id": "Q865"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_799_ab_en", "question": "Ashgabat was the capital of what from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Turkmenistan", "id": "Q874"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_800_ab_en", "question": "Damascus was the capital of what between 1945 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Syria", "id": "Q858"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_801_ab_en", "question": "Kinshasa was the capital of what from 1997 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Democratic Republic of the Congo", "id": "Q974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_802_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Aden from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Yemen", "id": "Q805"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_803_ab_en", "question": "Dushanbe was the capital of what from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tajikistan", "id": "Q863"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_804_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Salem between 1859 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Oregon", "id": "Q824"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_805_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Riyadh between 1819 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Saudi Arabia", "id": "Q851"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_806_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Jerusalem between 1950 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Israel", "id": "Q801"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_807_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Ciudad de la Paz from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Equatorial Guinea", "id": "Q983"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_808_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Islamabad from 1966 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Pakistan", "id": "Q843"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_809_ab_en", "question": "Malabo was the capital of what from 1968 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Equatorial Guinea", "id": "Q983"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_810_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Gitega from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Burundi", "id": "Q967"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_811_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Nicosia from 1960 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cyprus", "id": "Q229"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_812_ab_en", "question": "Riga was the capital of what from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Latvia", "id": "Q211"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_813_ab_en", "question": "Ljubljana was the capital of what from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Slovenia", "id": "Q215"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_814_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Tokyo from 1947 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_815_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Bern between 1848 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Switzerland", "id": "Q39"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_816_ab_en", "question": "Edo was the capital of what from 1603 to 1868?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_817_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Berlin from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Germany", "id": "Q183"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_818_ab_en", "question": "Cahaba was the capital of what between 1820 and 1825?", "answer": [{"label": "Alabama", "id": "Q173"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_819_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Turin from 1861 to 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "Italy", "id": "Q38"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_820_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Vichy from 1940 to 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "France", "id": "Q142"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_821_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Accra from 1961 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ghana", "id": "Q117"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_822_ab_en", "question": "Tokyo Prefecture was the capital of what from 1868 to 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_823_ab_en", "question": "Montevideo was the capital of what from 1828 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Uruguay", "id": "Q77"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_824_ab_en", "question": "Ankara was the capital of what from 1923 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Turkey", "id": "Q43"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_825_ab_en", "question": "Annapolis was the capital of what from 1783 to 1784?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_826_ab_en", "question": "Coimbra was the capital of what between 1129 and 1255?", "answer": [{"label": "Portugal", "id": "Q45"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_827_ab_en", "question": "Bonn was the capital of what from 1949 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Germany", "id": "Q183"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_828_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Tuscaloosa between 1826 and 1846?", "answer": [{"label": "Alabama", "id": "Q173"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_829_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Quebec City from 1867 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Quebec", "id": "Q176"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_830_ab_en", "question": "Rio de Janeiro was the capital of what between 1763 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "Brazil", "id": "Q155"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_831_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Tokyo City from 1889 to 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_832_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Helsinki between 1917 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Finland", "id": "Q33"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_833_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Vallejo between 1852 and 1853?", "answer": [{"label": "California", "id": "Q99"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_834_ab_en", "question": "Prague was the capital of what between 1993 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Czech Republic", "id": "Q213"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_835_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of New York City between 1785 and 1790?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_836_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Belfast between 1921 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Northern Ireland", "id": "Q26"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_837_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Dublin between 1937 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Republic of Ireland", "id": "Q27"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_838_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Kyoto between 794 and 1869?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_839_ab_en", "question": "San Jose was the capital of what from 1850 to 1851?", "answer": [{"label": "California", "id": "Q99"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_840_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Philadelphia from 1790 to 1800?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_841_ab_en", "question": "Budapest was the capital of what between 1989 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hungary", "id": "Q28"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_842_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Kutaisi between 2012 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Georgia", "id": "Q230"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_843_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Stockholm from 1436 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sweden", "id": "Q34"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_844_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Auckland from 1841 to 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "New Zealand", "id": "Q664"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_845_ab_en", "question": "Ngerulmud was the capital of what from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Palau", "id": "Q695"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_846_ab_en", "question": "Quito was the capital of what from 1830 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ecuador", "id": "Q736"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_847_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of New Delhi between 1947 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "India", "id": "Q668"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_848_ab_en", "question": "Pyongyang was the capital of what from 1948 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "North Korea", "id": "Q423"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_849_ab_en", "question": "Tegucigalpa was the capital of what from 1880 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Honduras", "id": "Q783"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_850_ab_en", "question": "Augusta was the capital of what between 1832 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Maine", "id": "Q724"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_851_ab_en", "question": "Kolonia was the capital of what between 1979 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "Federated States of Micronesia", "id": "Q702"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_852_ab_en", "question": "What was the capital of Melbourne from 1901 to 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "Australia", "id": "Q408"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_853_ab_en", "question": "Where was Dakar Rally located between 1979 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Africa", "id": "Q15"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_854_ab_en", "question": "Where was United Rugby Championship located between 2001 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Wales", "id": "Q25"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_855_ab_en", "question": "Dakar Rally took place in which location from 2009 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "South America", "id": "Q18"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_856_ab_en", "question": "Central Group of Forces took place in which location from 1945 to 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "Hungary", "id": "Q28"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_857_ab_en", "question": "Where was United Rugby Championship taking place from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Italy", "id": "Q38"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_858_ab_en", "question": "Where was Central Group of Forces taking place between 1945 and 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "Austria", "id": "Q40"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_859_ab_en", "question": "Where was Wiki Education Foundation located between 2013 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "San Francisco", "id": "Q62"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_860_ab_en", "question": "Black Death took place in which location between 1338 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Asia", "id": "Q48"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_861_ab_en", "question": "Where was Songs of David Byrne and Brian Eno Tour taking place during 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Asia", "id": "Q48"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_862_ab_en", "question": "Where was Goddard Institute for Space Studies taking place from 1961 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_863_ab_en", "question": "Songs of David Byrne and Brian Eno Tour took place in which location in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "North America", "id": "Q49"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_864_ab_en", "question": "Where was Normandy Format located in the year of 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_865_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by European Union between 1973 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Denmark", "id": "Q35"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_866_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by European Union between 1973 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Republic of Ireland", "id": "Q27"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_867_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by German Confederation between 1815 and 1866?", "answer": [{"label": "Luxembourg", "id": "Q32"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_868_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by United Kingdom from 1921 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Northern Ireland", "id": "Q26"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_869_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by United States of America between 1788 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New Hampshire", "id": "Q759"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_870_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by United States of America from 1788 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Massachusetts", "id": "Q771"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_871_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Confederate States from 1861 to 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "Alabama", "id": "Q173"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_872_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by District of Columbia from 1802 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_873_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Germany from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_874_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by District of Columbia from 1790 to 1846?", "answer": [{"label": "Alexandria", "id": "Q88"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_875_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Yvelines between 1968 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Versailles", "id": "Q621"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_876_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Lille metropolis from 1967 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lille", "id": "Q648"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_877_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Yvelines from 1968 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Poissy", "id": "Q457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_878_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by German Confederation between 1815 and 1866?", "answer": [{"label": "Liechtenstein", "id": "Q347"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_879_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Sumatra between 1957 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Padang Pariaman", "id": "Q6042"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_880_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Sumatra from 1957 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tanah Datar", "id": "Q6093"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_881_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Kuusiokunnat from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kuortane", "id": "Q6012"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_882_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Kuusiokunnat from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ähtäri", "id": "Q6172"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_883_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Suupohja from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kauhajoki", "id": "Q5992"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_884_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Suupohja between 1994 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Teuva", "id": "Q6167"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_885_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Germany between 1952 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Baden-Württemberg", "id": "Q985"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_886_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Germany from 1952 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Baden-Württemberg", "id": "Q985"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_887_ab_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Germany from 1949 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Bavaria", "id": "Q980"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_888_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Gian Piero Ventura between 1999 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_889_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Peter Bosz from 2021 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympique Lyonnais", "id": "Q704"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_890_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Ottavio Bianchi between 1994 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_891_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Marco Giampaolo from 2016 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_892_ab_en", "question": "Andrea Pirlo was the coach of which team from 2020 to 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_893_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Arrigo Sacchi from 1987 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "AC Milan", "id": "Q1543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_894_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Dino Zoff between 1988 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_895_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Marcello Lippi between 2001 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_896_ab_en", "question": "Antonio Conte was the coach of which team between 2019 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_897_ab_en", "question": "Eugenio Bersellini was the coach of which team between 1975 and 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_898_ab_en", "question": "Giuseppe Meazza was the coach of which team in 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_899_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Laurent Blanc from 2022 to 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympique Lyonnais", "id": "Q704"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_900_ab_en", "question": "Arrigo Sacchi was the coach of which team between 1996 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "AC Milan", "id": "Q1543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_901_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Antonio Conte between 2011 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_902_ab_en", "question": "Walter Zenga was the coach of which team in 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_903_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Didier Deschamps between 2006 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_904_ab_en", "question": "Eugenio Bersellini was the coach of which team between 1984 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_905_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Fabio Capello from 2004 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_906_ab_en", "question": "Armando Castellazzi was the coach of which team between 1936 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_907_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Simone Inzaghi from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_908_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Helenio Herrera from 1973 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_909_ab_en", "question": "Carlo Ancelotti was the coach of which team between 1999 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_910_ab_en", "question": "Stefano Pioli was the coach of which team from 2016 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_911_ab_en", "question": "Luciano Spalletti was the coach of which team in the year of 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_912_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Claudio Ranieri between 2019 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_913_ab_en", "question": "Giovanni Trapattoni was the coach of which team between 1976 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_914_ab_en", "question": "Roberto Mancini was the coach of which team from 2004 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_915_ab_en", "question": "Claudio Ranieri was the coach of which team between 2011 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_916_ab_en", "question": "Walter Mazzarri was the coach of which team from 2007 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_917_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Luciano Spalletti during 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_918_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Marcello Lippi from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_919_ab_en", "question": "Eusebio Di Francesco was the coach of which team between 2020 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_920_ab_en", "question": "Andrea Pirlo was the coach of which team between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_921_ab_en", "question": "Massimiliano Allegri was the coach of which team from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_922_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Luigi Simoni between 1997 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_923_ab_en", "question": "Angelo Alessio was the coach of which team during 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_924_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Frank de Boer in the year of 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_925_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Sylvinho in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympique Lyonnais", "id": "Q704"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_926_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Massimiliano Allegri between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_927_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Fabio Grosso in the year of 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympique Lyonnais", "id": "Q704"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_928_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Giuseppe Meazza from 1955 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_929_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Helenio Herrera between 1960 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_930_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Roy Hodgson during 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_931_ab_en", "question": "Giovanni Trapattoni was the coach of which team between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_932_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Luigi Radice between 1983 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_933_ab_en", "question": "Fabrizio Ravanelli was the coach of which team from 2011 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_934_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Maurizio Sarri between 2019 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_935_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Vincenzo Montella between 2015 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "U.C. Sampdoria", "id": "Q1457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_936_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Roberto Mancini from 2014 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_937_ab_en", "question": "Roy Hodgson was the coach of which team between 1995 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_938_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Walter Mazzarri from 2013 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Inter Milan", "id": "Q631"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_939_ab_en", "question": "Thiago Motta was the coach of which team in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Genoa CFC", "id": "Q2074"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_940_ab_en", "question": "Thiago Motta was the coach of which team between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bologna F.C. 1909", "id": "Q1893"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_941_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Rolando Maran from 2012 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Catania F.C.", "id": "Q2018"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_942_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Ottavio Bianchi from 1981 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "Atalanta BC", "id": "Q1886"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_943_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Andriy Shevchenko between 2021 and 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Genoa CFC", "id": "Q2074"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_944_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Vincenzo Montella from 2012 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "ACF Fiorentina", "id": "Q2052"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_945_ab_en", "question": "Luigi Radice was the coach of which team from 1980 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "Bologna F.C. 1909", "id": "Q1893"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_946_ab_en", "question": "Nedo Sonetti was the coach of which team between 2005 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Cagliari Calcio", "id": "Q1900"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_947_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Andrea Mandorlini from 2005 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Bologna F.C. 1909", "id": "Q1893"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_948_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Nedo Sonetti from 2001 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Cagliari Calcio", "id": "Q1900"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_949_ab_en", "question": "Aldo Agroppi was the coach of which team between 1985 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "ACF Fiorentina", "id": "Q2052"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_950_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Stefano Pioli between 2011 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Bologna F.C. 1909", "id": "Q1893"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_951_ab_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Diego Pablo Simeone in 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Catania F.C.", "id": "Q2018"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_952_ab_en", "question": "Franco Scoglio was the coach of which team during 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "Genoa CFC", "id": "Q2074"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_953_ab_en", "question": "Franco Scoglio was the coach of which team between 1988 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Genoa CFC", "id": "Q2074"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_954_ab_en", "question": "Rolando Maran was the coach of which team between 2018 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Cagliari Calcio", "id": "Q1900"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_955_ab_en", "question": "Aurelio Andreazzoli was the coach of which team during 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Genoa CFC", "id": "Q2074"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_956_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Russi Taylor from 1989 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "The Simpsons", "id": "Q886"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_957_ab_en", "question": "Leslie Jones published which notable work between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Saturday Night Live", "id": "Q13979"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_958_ab_en", "question": "Benjamin Henry Latrobe published which notable work from 1803 to 1817?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Capitol", "id": "Q54109"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_959_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Owen Wilson from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cars", "id": "Q182153"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_960_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Holly Robinson Peete from 1987 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "21 Jump Street", "id": "Q214016"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_961_ab_en", "question": "Savannah Guthrie published which notable work from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_962_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Al Roker between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_963_ab_en", "question": "Barbara Walters published which notable work from 1962 to 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_964_ab_en", "question": "Tamron Hall published which notable work between 2014 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_965_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Katie Couric between 1991 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_966_ab_en", "question": "Frank McGee published which notable work from 1971 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_967_ab_en", "question": "Meredith Vieira published which notable work between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_968_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Seth Rogen between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kung Fu Panda", "id": "Q129193"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_969_ab_en", "question": "Hoda Kotb published which notable work from 2008 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Today", "id": "Q130838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_970_ab_en", "question": "James Earl Jones published which notable work between 1994 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "The Lion King", "id": "Q36479"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_971_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Arianna Huffington between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "The Cleveland Show", "id": "Q34397"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_972_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Russell T Davies from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Doctor Who", "id": "Q34316"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_973_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Lennon Stella from 2012 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Nashville", "id": "Q210676"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_974_ab_en", "question": "David Bates Douglass published which notable work between 1838 and 1841?", "answer": [{"label": "Green-Wood Cemetery", "id": "Q239043"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_975_ab_en", "question": "Sara Gilbert published which notable work from 2007 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "The Big Bang Theory", "id": "Q8539"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_976_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by John Cleese from 2001 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Harry Potter", "id": "Q216930"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_977_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Dylan Sprouse between 2005 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "The Suite Life of Zack & Cody", "id": "Q217246"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_978_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Cole Sprouse from 2005 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "The Suite Life of Zack & Cody", "id": "Q217246"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_979_ab_en", "question": "Geoffrey Rush published which notable work between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Pirates of the Caribbean", "id": "Q194318"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_980_ab_en", "question": "Ferdinand Boberg published which notable work from 1907 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Thiel Gallery", "id": "Q252259"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_981_ab_en", "question": "Heather Locklear published which notable work from 1999 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Spin City", "id": "Q256527"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_982_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Connie Britton from 1996 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Spin City", "id": "Q256527"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_983_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Ellen DeGeneres from 1994 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Ellen", "id": "Q82226"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_984_ab_en", "question": "Morley Safer published which notable work between 1970 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "60 Minutes", "id": "Q247869"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_985_ab_en", "question": "Mike Wallace published which notable work from 1968 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "60 Minutes", "id": "Q247869"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_986_ab_en", "question": "Meredith Vieira published which notable work from 1989 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "60 Minutes", "id": "Q247869"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_987_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Shannen Doherty between 1990 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Beverly Hills, 90210", "id": "Q117590"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_988_ab_en", "question": "Vanessa Marcil published which notable work from 1998 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Beverly Hills, 90210", "id": "Q117590"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_989_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Tyra Banks between 2003 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "America's Next Top Model", "id": "Q31426"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_990_ab_en", "question": "William Shatner published which notable work from 1982 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "T. J. Hooker", "id": "Q178724"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_991_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Heather Locklear from 1982 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "T. J. Hooker", "id": "Q178724"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_992_ab_en", "question": "Barbara Walters published which notable work between 1979 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "20/20", "id": "Q197867"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_993_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Luigi Cagnola from 1818 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Äußeres Burgtor", "id": "Q258347"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_994_ab_en", "question": "NHK published which notable work between 1951 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kōhaku Uta Gassen", "id": "Q257913"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_995_ab_en", "question": "Kourtney Kardashian published which notable work between 2007 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Keeping Up with the Kardashians", "id": "Q152108"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_996_ab_en", "question": "Andrzej Pszenicki published which notable work from 1912 to 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "Palace Bridge", "id": "Q148970"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_997_ab_en", "question": "Rob Kardashian published which notable work from 2007 to 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Keeping Up with the Kardashians", "id": "Q152108"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_998_ab_en", "question": "Piero Portaluppi published which notable work between 1919 and 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "Pinacoteca di Brera", "id": "Q150066"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_999_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Naya Rivera between 2009 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Glee", "id": "Q152178"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1000_ab_en", "question": "Kris Jenner published which notable work between 2007 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Keeping Up with the Kardashians", "id": "Q152108"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1001_ab_en", "question": "Scott Disick published which notable work between 2007 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Keeping Up with the Kardashians", "id": "Q152108"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1002_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Alyssa Milano between 1998 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Charmed", "id": "Q162371"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1003_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Holly Marie Combs between 1998 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Charmed", "id": "Q162371"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1004_ab_en", "question": "Rose McGowan published which notable work between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Charmed", "id": "Q162371"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1005_ab_en", "question": "Frank Welker published which notable work from 1969 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Scooby-Doo", "id": "Q205683"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1006_ab_en", "question": "Tamara Taylor published which notable work from 2006 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Bones", "id": "Q207803"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1007_ab_en", "question": "Don Messick published which notable work between 1969 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Scooby-Doo", "id": "Q205683"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1008_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Matthew Lillard between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Scooby-Doo", "id": "Q205683"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1009_ab_en", "question": "Charles Jennens published which notable work from 1741 to 1742?", "answer": [{"label": "Messiah", "id": "Q207732"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1010_ab_en", "question": "China Anne McClain published which notable work between 2011 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "A.N.T. Farm", "id": "Q278375"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1011_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Candice Bergen from 2005 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Boston Legal", "id": "Q308984"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1012_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Zendaya from 2010 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Shake It Up", "id": "Q308700"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1013_ab_en", "question": "Rollan Martirosov published which notable work between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sukhoi Su-34", "id": "Q309177"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1014_ab_en", "question": "Everett Rogers published which notable work between 1962 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "diffusion of innovations", "id": "Q304994"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1015_ab_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Nippon Broadcasting System between 1967 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "All Night Nippon", "id": "Q282630"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1016_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino between 1963 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Torino Football Club", "id": "Q2768"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1017_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino between 1958 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "Torino Football Club", "id": "Q2768"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1018_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Giuseppe Meazza Stadium between 2018 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Atalanta BC", "id": "Q1886"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1019_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio Olimpico between 1953 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "A.S. Roma", "id": "Q2739"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1020_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Olimpico between 1953 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "S.S. Lazio", "id": "Q2609"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1021_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio delle Alpi between 1990 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Juventus FC", "id": "Q1422"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1022_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio delle Alpi from 1990 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Torino Football Club", "id": "Q2768"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1023_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Flaminio between 1989 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "A.S. Roma", "id": "Q2739"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1024_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Flaminio from 1989 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "S.S. Lazio", "id": "Q2609"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1025_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Giuseppe Meazza Stadium between 1926 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "AC Milan", "id": "Q1543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1026_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied One Times Square from 1905 to 1913?", "answer": [{"label": "The New York Times", "id": "Q9684"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1027_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Birthplace of Richard Nixon from 1913 to 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard Nixon", "id": "Q9588"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1028_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of RAF Burtonwood between 1967 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1029_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Arsenal Stadium between 1913 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Arsenal F.C.", "id": "Q9617"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1030_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Barnet Copthall from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Saracens F.C.", "id": "Q9641"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1031_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied MEK Compound between 2003 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1032_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Fort Frederiksborg between 1679 and 1700?", "answer": [{"label": "British Empire", "id": "Q8680"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1033_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Marlborough House between 1965 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Commonwealth of Nations", "id": "Q7785"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1034_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Eurotower from 1998 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "European Central Bank", "id": "Q8901"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1035_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Cape Coast Castle from 1664 to 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "British Empire", "id": "Q8680"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1036_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Montjuic Olympic Stadium between 1997 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "RCD Espanyol de Barcelona", "id": "Q8780"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1037_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Royal Palace of Amsterdam from 1808 to 1810?", "answer": [{"label": "Louis Bonaparte", "id": "Q7729"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1038_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio Alberto Braglia from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "U.S. Sassuolo Calcio", "id": "Q8603"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1039_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Rembrandt House Museum from 1639 to 1658?", "answer": [{"label": "Rembrandt", "id": "Q5598"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1040_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Anfield from 1884 to 1892?", "answer": [{"label": "Everton F.C.", "id": "Q5794"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1041_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Braunes Haus between 1931 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nazi Party", "id": "Q7320"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1042_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Montjuic Olympic Stadium from 2023 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "FC Barcelona", "id": "Q7156"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1043_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Charlottenhof Palace from 1835 to 1840?", "answer": [{"label": "Alexander von Humboldt", "id": "Q6694"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1044_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Einsteinhaus from 1903 to 1905?", "answer": [{"label": "Albert Einstein", "id": "Q937"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1045_ab_en", "question": "Who occupied Bolshiye Gorki from 1918 to 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "Vladimir Lenin", "id": "Q1394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1046_ab_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Berghof between 1928 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Adolf Hitler", "id": "Q352"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1047_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of World Union for Progressive Judaism was located in where between 1959 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1048_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Fawcett Publications was located in where from 1935 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1049_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Automobile Manufacturers Association located from 1911 to 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1050_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Erie Railroad located between 1832 and 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1051_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of College Art Association was located in where from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1052_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Fleischer Studios located between 1923 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1053_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Foot Locker was located in where from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1054_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Doghouse Records located between 2005 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1055_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of American Petroleum Institute was located in where between 1919 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1056_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Standard Oil located from 1885 to 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1057_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Nickelodeon Animation Studio located between 1999 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1058_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of MetLife was located in where between 1909 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1059_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of American Association for Justice located between 1977 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1060_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of United Aircraft and Transport Corporation located between 1929 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1061_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of United States Census Bureau was located in where between 1902 and 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1062_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of American Petroleum Institute was located in where from 1969 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1063_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Code for America was located in where from 2012 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "San Francisco", "id": "Q62"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1064_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Code for America was located in where between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "San Francisco", "id": "Q62"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1065_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Port Authority of New York and New Jersey was located in where between 2001 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1066_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Port Authority of New York and New Jersey was located in where between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1067_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Air Force Global Strike Command located between 1944 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1068_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of United States Department of Commerce was located in where between 1932 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1069_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Supreme Court of the United States located between 1935 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1070_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Gallup located from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1071_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Washington Spirit was located in where from 2018 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1072_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of Mozilla Corporation was located in where from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "San Francisco", "id": "Q62"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1073_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of China Zhi Gong Party located between 1925 and 1926?", "answer": [{"label": "San Francisco", "id": "Q62"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1074_ab_en", "question": "The headquarter of SVB Financial Group was located in where between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1075_ab_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of The Baffler located between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1076_ab_en", "question": "Who performed M from 1995 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Judi Dench", "id": "Q28054"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1077_ab_en", "question": "Who performed M between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ralph Fiennes", "id": "Q28493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1078_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Lord Voldemort from 2005 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Ralph Fiennes", "id": "Q28493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1079_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Shaggy Rogers from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Matthew Lillard", "id": "Q29086"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1080_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Q from 1963 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Desmond Llewelyn", "id": "Q29092"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1081_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Princess Protection Program during 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Demi Lovato", "id": "Q41173"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1082_ab_en", "question": "Another Cinderella Story was performed by whom in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Selena Gomez", "id": "Q83287"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1083_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Greg Heffley between 2010 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Zachary Gordon", "id": "Q139611"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1084_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Linda Perry from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "4 Non Blondes", "id": "Q238263"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1085_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Lord Voldemort in 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Eddie Izzard", "id": "Q254022"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1086_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Lola Bunny from 1996 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Kath Soucie", "id": "Q262910"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1087_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Hello Kitty from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Megumi Hayashibara", "id": "Q266670"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1088_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Winnie the Pooh between 1988 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jim Cummings", "id": "Q310292"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1089_ab_en", "question": "Mickey Mouse was performed by whom from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Chris Diamantopoulos", "id": "Q311980"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1090_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Gopher from 1966 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "Howard Morris", "id": "Q322266"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1091_ab_en", "question": "Q was performed by whom between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ben Whishaw", "id": "Q342617"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1092_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Donald Duck between 1934 and 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "Clarence Nash", "id": "Q372838"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1093_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Lola Bunny between 2002 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Britt McKillip", "id": "Q458871"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1094_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Gomez Addams between 1964 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "John Astin", "id": "Q458464"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1095_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Mac Tonight from 1986 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Doug Jones", "id": "Q461309"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1096_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Oscar the Grouch from 1969 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Caroll Spinney", "id": "Q561765"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1097_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Scooter from 1976 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard Hunt", "id": "Q561809"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1098_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Luigi between 1992 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles Martinet", "id": "Q703384"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1099_ab_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Doctor Eggman from 1993 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Long John Baldry", "id": "Q712880"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1100_ab_en", "question": "Winnie the Pooh was performed by whom from 1966 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "Sterling Holloway", "id": "Q725507"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1101_ab_en", "question": "Who performed Donald Duck from 1985 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tony Anselmo", "id": "Q719196"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1102_ab_en", "question": "Pluto was performed by whom between 1931 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "Pinto Colvig", "id": "Q945591"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1103_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Pangyo Station between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeongja Station", "id": "Q31038"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1104_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Migeum Station between 1994 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeongja Station", "id": "Q31038"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1105_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Wangsimni Station between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Seoul Forest Station", "id": "Q24058"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1106_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Wangsimni Station between 1911 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cheongnyangni Station", "id": "Q20417"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1107_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Tai Po Kau railway station between 1910 and 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "Sha Tin station", "id": "Q15242"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1108_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Sinnonhyeon Station between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Gangnam Station", "id": "Q17469"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1109_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Ori Station from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jukjeon Station", "id": "Q17226"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1110_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Yangjae Station from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Gangnam Station", "id": "Q17469"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1111_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Bojeong Station from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jukjeon Station", "id": "Q17226"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1112_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Ori Station between 2004 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Bojeong Station", "id": "Q46203"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1113_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Jukjeon Station from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bojeong Station", "id": "Q46203"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1114_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Jeongja Station from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Migeum Station", "id": "Q46193"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1115_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Jeongja Station from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sunae Station", "id": "Q46201"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1116_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Dongcheon Station from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Migeum Station", "id": "Q46193"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1117_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Pangyo Station from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Imae Station", "id": "Q46188"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1118_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Imae Station from 2004 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Yatap Station", "id": "Q46186"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1119_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Imae Station between 2004 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Seohyeon Station", "id": "Q46190"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1120_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Gangnam Station from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sinnonhyeon Station", "id": "Q53000"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1121_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Nonhyeon Station between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sinnonhyeon Station", "id": "Q53000"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1122_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Yoyogi Station between 2000 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kokuritsu-Kyōgijō Station", "id": "Q275113"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1123_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Songjiazhuang station between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Chengshou Si station", "id": "Q75393"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1124_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Jamsil Station between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Seokchon Station", "id": "Q75339"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1125_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Jamsil Station between 1999 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Mongchontoseong Station", "id": "Q75328"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1126_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Gongzhufen station from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lianhua Qiao station", "id": "Q75398"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1127_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Cishou Si station between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Chedaogou station", "id": "Q75264"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1128_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Keisei Tsudanuma Station between 1953 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Shin-Tsudanuma Station", "id": "Q285362"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1129_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Nonhyeon Station from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sinsa Station", "id": "Q100839"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1130_ab_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Yangjae Station from 1985 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nambu Bus Terminal Station", "id": "Q100848"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1131_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Gangnam Station between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Yangjae Station", "id": "Q100852"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1132_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Sosa Station from 2023 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bucheon Stadium Station", "id": "Q69052"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1133_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Sinsa Station from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nonhyeon Station", "id": "Q68920"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1134_ab_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Sinnonhyeon Station between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nonhyeon Station", "id": "Q68920"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1135_ab_en", "question": "WWE NXT was presented by whom from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Shawn Michaels", "id": "Q31317"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1136_ab_en", "question": "Robot Wars was presented by whom in 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeremy Clarkson", "id": "Q216160"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1137_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Late Show with Stephen Colbert between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Colbert", "id": "Q212886"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1138_ab_en", "question": "The Daily Show Mondays with Jon Stewart was presented by whom during 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jon Stewart", "id": "Q211987"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1139_ab_en", "question": "The Colbert Report was presented by whom from 2005 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Colbert", "id": "Q212886"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1140_ab_en", "question": "The Daily Show Mondays with Jon Stewart was presented by whom between 1999 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Jon Stewart", "id": "Q211987"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1141_ab_en", "question": "Top Gear was presented by whom between 2002 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeremy Clarkson", "id": "Q216160"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1142_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of Sportschau from 1988 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "Reinhold Beckmann", "id": "Q103858"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1143_ab_en", "question": "Sportschau was presented by whom between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Reinhold Beckmann", "id": "Q103858"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1144_ab_en", "question": "Tagesthemen was presented by whom between 1978 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "Wolf von Lojewski", "id": "Q105011"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1145_ab_en", "question": "Today was presented by whom from 1980 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Willard Scott", "id": "Q313464"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1146_ab_en", "question": "To Tell the Truth was presented by whom between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Anthony Anderson", "id": "Q313918"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1147_ab_en", "question": "Top Gear was presented by whom from 2003 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "James May", "id": "Q314504"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1148_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of Card Sharks between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Joel McHale", "id": "Q311993"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1149_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Tonight Show between 1962 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "Johnny Carson", "id": "Q310819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1150_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Tonight Show from 1992 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Jay Leno", "id": "Q218718"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1151_ab_en", "question": "The Voice of Germany was presented by whom from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Thore Schölermann", "id": "Q70879"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1152_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of Tagesthemen from 1991 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Ulrich Wickert", "id": "Q71490"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1153_ab_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Late Late Show with James Corden between 2005 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Craig Ferguson", "id": "Q72867"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1154_ab_en", "question": "Where was Emile Guillemin exhibited between 1870 and 1899?", "answer": [{"label": "Louvre Museum", "id": "Q19675"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1155_ab_en", "question": "Where was Madonna of Jacob Floreins exhibited in the year of 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "Louvre Museum", "id": "Q19675"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1156_ab_en", "question": "Where was Antonio Rotta exhibited between 1898 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hermitage Museum", "id": "Q132783"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1157_ab_en", "question": "Where was The Return of the Prodigal Son exhibited from 1767 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hermitage Museum", "id": "Q132783"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1158_ab_en", "question": "Where was Boxer at Rest exhibited in the year of 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Metropolitan Museum of Art", "id": "Q160236"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1159_ab_en", "question": "nihonium was named after what between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1160_ab_en", "question": "Washington was named after what between 1837 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "George Washington", "id": "Q23"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1161_ab_en", "question": "Lincoln was named after what from 1867 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Abraham Lincoln", "id": "Q91"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1162_ab_en", "question": "Pariser Platz was named after what between 1814 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Paris", "id": "Q90"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1163_ab_en", "question": "Lincoln was named after what between 1853 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Abraham Lincoln", "id": "Q91"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1164_ab_en", "question": "Central do Brasil was named after what between 1971 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Brazil", "id": "Q155"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1165_ab_en", "question": "hydrogen was named after what from 1783 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "water", "id": "Q283"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1166_ab_en", "question": "Chornomorsk was named after what between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Black Sea", "id": "Q166"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1167_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Niels between 1104 and 1134?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1168_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Tristan from 560 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1169_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of George I of Great Britain between 1714 and 1727?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1170_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Saban in the year of 234?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1171_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Christian IX of Denmark between 1863 and 1906?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1172_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Daru between 28 and 77?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1173_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Giru from 77 to 128?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1174_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Gaeru from 128 to 166?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1175_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Goi between 234 and 286?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1176_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Gusu between 214 and 234?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1177_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Chogo between 166 and 214?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1178_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Rudolf Duala Manga Bell between 1908 and 1914?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1179_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Ndumbe Lobe Bell from 1858 to 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1180_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Stotzas between 541 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "king", "id": "Q12097"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1181_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Rasoherina I of Madagascar from 1863 to 1868?", "answer": [{"label": "queen regnant", "id": "Q19643"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1182_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Ranavalona II of Madagascar between 1868 and 1883?", "answer": [{"label": "queen regnant", "id": "Q19643"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1183_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Rudrama Devi between 1263 and 1289?", "answer": [{"label": "queen regnant", "id": "Q19643"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1184_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Margrethe II of Denmark between 1972 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "queen regnant", "id": "Q19643"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1185_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Frederick William von Hessenstein from 1785 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Fürst", "id": "Q18244"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1186_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Otto Magnus von Stackelberg between 1775 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "graf", "id": "Q28989"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1187_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Florent van Ertborn from 1816 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "knight", "id": "Q102083"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1188_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Emperor Norton from 1859 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "emperor", "id": "Q39018"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1189_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Emperor Zhenzong of Song from 997 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "emperor", "id": "Q39018"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1190_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Liu Shan between 223 and 263?", "answer": [{"label": "emperor", "id": "Q39018"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1191_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Kharak Singh from 1839 to 1840?", "answer": [{"label": "emperor", "id": "Q39018"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1192_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Charles I of Bourbon between 1434 and 1456?", "answer": [{"label": "graf", "id": "Q28989"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1193_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Raymond Ceulemans from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "knight", "id": "Q102083"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1194_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of William Alexander Smith from 1909 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "knight", "id": "Q102083"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1195_ab_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Ashton Lever from 1778 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "knight", "id": "Q102083"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1196_ab_en", "question": "Rheinische Zeitung was edited by whom from 1942 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Karl Marx", "id": "Q9061"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1197_ab_en", "question": "Sovremennik was edited by whom from 1836 to 1837?", "answer": [{"label": "Alexander Pushkin", "id": "Q7200"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1198_ab_en", "question": "Who was the editor of Great Soviet Encyclopedia from 1969 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "Alexander Prokhorov", "id": "Q83552"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1199_ab_en", "question": "Who was the editor of Playboy from 1953 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Hugh Hefner", "id": "Q194280"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1200_ab_en", "question": "Who was the editor of Byzantinische Zeitschrift from 1991 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Peter Schreiner", "id": "Q98564"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1201_ab_en", "question": "Byzantinische Zeitschrift was edited by whom from 1892 to 1909?", "answer": [{"label": "Karl Krumbacher", "id": "Q61463"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1202_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Ken Block participate from 2007 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "World Rally Championship", "id": "Q7852"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1203_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did John Franklin participate between 1845 and 1848?", "answer": [{"label": "Franklin's lost expedition", "id": "Q2305"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1204_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Romain Grosjean participate between 2009 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1205_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Felipe Massa participate from 2002 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1206_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did George Russell participate between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1207_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Jens Fiedler participate in the year of 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "1992 Summer Olympics", "id": "Q8488"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1208_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Maria Sole Ferrieri Caputi participate from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "UEFA", "id": "Q35572"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1209_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Leo Franco participate in 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "2006 FIFA World Cup", "id": "Q37285"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1210_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Abraham Pomerantz participate from 1946 to 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "Nuremberg trials", "id": "Q80130"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1211_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Clarence Campbell participate from 1945 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Nuremberg trials", "id": "Q80130"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1212_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Eberhard Godt participate between 1945 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "Nuremberg trials", "id": "Q80130"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1213_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Vladimir Putin participate from 1999 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Second Chechen War", "id": "Q120843"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1214_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Holger Rune participate between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Davis Cup", "id": "Q132377"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1215_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Arthur Rinderknech participate between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Davis Cup", "id": "Q132377"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1216_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did George Russell participate during 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "GP3 Series", "id": "Q149844"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1217_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Eirik Kristoffersen participate from 1991 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "United Nations Interim Force in Lebanon", "id": "Q160805"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1218_ab_en", "question": "Which campaign did Maria Sole Ferrieri Caputi participate between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Coppa Italia", "id": "Q169918"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1219_ab_en", "question": "Who was the commander of XIV Corps from 1870 to 1879?", "answer": [{"label": "August von Werder", "id": "Q64634"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1220_ab_en", "question": "Who commanded Mediterranean Division from 1913 to 1914?", "answer": [{"label": "Wilhelm Souchon", "id": "Q62450"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1221_ab_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Admiral Scheer from 1939 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "Theodor Krancke", "id": "Q67790"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1222_ab_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Guards Cavalry Division between 1826 and 1838?", "answer": [{"label": "Friedrich Wilhelm, Count Brandenburg", "id": "Q65053"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1223_ab_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Guards Cavalry Division from 1856 to 1859?", "answer": [{"label": "Prince August of Württemberg", "id": "Q64613"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1224_ab_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Admiral Scheer between 1936 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "Otto Ciliax", "id": "Q62743"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1225_ab_en", "question": "Who commanded German battleship Scharnhorst in the year of 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "Otto Ciliax", "id": "Q62743"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1226_ab_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Warsaw Pact from 1977 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "Viktor Kulikov", "id": "Q48051"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1227_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Shell from 2009 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Peter Voser", "id": "Q116012"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1228_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Volkswagen Group between 1982 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "Carl Hahn", "id": "Q97087"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1229_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of New America between 2007 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Steve Coll", "id": "Q128771"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1230_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Pirelli between 1986 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Marco Tronchetti Provera", "id": "Q144191"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1231_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Robert Bosch between 2003 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Franz Fehrenbach", "id": "Q108902"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1232_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of The Swatch Group between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nick Hayek", "id": "Q117407"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1233_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of UBS from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sergio Ermotti", "id": "Q117289"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1234_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Monetary Fund from 1956 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "Per Jacobsson", "id": "Q176113"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1235_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Formula One between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Stefano Domenicali", "id": "Q173168"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1236_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Westdeutscher Rundfunk from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tom Buhrow", "id": "Q108634"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1237_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Microsoft from 2000 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Steve Ballmer", "id": "Q181162"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1238_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Siemens between 2005 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Heinrich von Pierer", "id": "Q96770"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1239_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Telegram between 2013 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Pavel Valeryevich Durov", "id": "Q149067"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1240_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Siemens from 1992 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Heinrich von Pierer", "id": "Q96770"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1241_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Happy Madison Productions between 1999 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Adam Sandler", "id": "Q132952"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1242_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Audi AG from 2006 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Rupert Stadler", "id": "Q107639"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1243_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Hilton Worldwide between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nicky Hilton", "id": "Q216298"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1244_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of The Swatch Group from 1986 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Nicolas Hayek", "id": "Q123692"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1245_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Commerzbank AG between 2008 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Martin Blessing", "id": "Q112942"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1246_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Porsche between 1981 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "Peter Schutz", "id": "Q102444"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1247_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Pacific FC from 2018 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Rob Friend", "id": "Q128870"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1248_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Fidelity Investments between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Abigail Johnson", "id": "Q321125"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1249_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Mistwalker from 2004 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Hironobu Sakaguchi", "id": "Q312525"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1250_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Heineken from 1971 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "Freddy Heineken", "id": "Q321149"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1251_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Monetary Fund from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kristalina Georgieva", "id": "Q265277"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1252_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Federal Agency on Atomic Energy from 2005 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Sergey Kiriyenko", "id": "Q313915"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1253_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Ford Motor Company between 2006 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Alan Mulally", "id": "Q348874"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1254_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Shell between 2005 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeroen van der Veer", "id": "Q354962"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1255_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of The Walt Disney Company from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Roy O. Disney", "id": "Q347432"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1256_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Apple between 1981 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "Mike Markkula", "id": "Q369783"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1257_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of General Electric between 1981 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "Jack Welch", "id": "Q355314"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1258_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Abbott Laboratories between 1999 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Miles D. White", "id": "Q281657"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1259_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of PepsiCo between 2006 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Indra Nooyi", "id": "Q264913"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1260_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of HM Treasury from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeremy Hunt", "id": "Q333533"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1261_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Amazon between 1996 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Jeff Bezos", "id": "Q312556"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1262_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Bank for Reconstruction and Development from 2017 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Kristalina Georgieva", "id": "Q265277"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1263_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Suzanne Greco between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Subway", "id": "Q244457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1264_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Intel between 1975 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "Gordon Moore", "id": "Q243969"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1265_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of SRI International from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Karl August Folkers", "id": "Q268874"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1266_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of HSBC from 2003 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Stephen Green, Baron Green of Hurstpierpoint", "id": "Q335910"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1267_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of TotalEnergies from 2007 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Christophe de Margerie", "id": "Q346081"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1268_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of ExxonMobil from 1999 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Lee Raymond", "id": "Q359908"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1269_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of eBay between 2008 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "John Donahoe", "id": "Q267074"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1270_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Development Association between 2017 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Kristalina Georgieva", "id": "Q265277"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1271_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Society of Jesus between 2008 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Adolfo Nicolás", "id": "Q365131"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1272_ab_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Nvidia from 1993 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jensen Huang", "id": "Q305177"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1273_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of PSL University between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "École Normale Supérieure", "id": "Q83259"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1274_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Turner Broadcasting System from 1994 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "New Line Cinema", "id": "Q79202"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1275_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Groupe PSA between 2017 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vauxhall", "id": "Q59187"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1276_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Stellantis between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vauxhall", "id": "Q59187"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1277_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Grupo Globo from 1965 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "TV Globo", "id": "Q3587"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1278_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of University of Lyon between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Jean Moulin University - Lyon 3", "id": "Q4027"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1279_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of University of Lyon from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lumière University Lyon 2", "id": "Q4041"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1280_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Stellantis from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Peugeot", "id": "Q6742"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1281_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of RCA Corporation from 1926 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1282_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Saban Capital Group between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Panavision", "id": "Q11289"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1283_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Community of universities and higher education institutions of Aquitaine between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bordeaux Montaigne University", "id": "Q13342"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1284_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Community of universities and higher education institutions of Aquitaine from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Bordeaux", "id": "Q13344"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1285_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Leonardo da Vinci consolidated University from 2015 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Orléans", "id": "Q13334"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1286_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of United States Department of the Air Force between 1947 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Air Force", "id": "Q11223"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1287_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Communist International from 1922 to 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "Chinese Communist Party", "id": "Q17427"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1288_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Radio France from 1974 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "Radio France Internationale", "id": "Q19912"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1289_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Studebaker from 1928 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Pierce-Arrow", "id": "Q40978"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1290_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Pershing Square Holdings between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1291_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of CBS Corporation between 2005 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "CBS", "id": "Q43380"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1292_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of ABB Group between 1988 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "ABB Oy", "id": "Q41461"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1293_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Tata Motors Ltd between 2008 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Land Rover", "id": "Q35907"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1294_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of AMR Corporation between 1982 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "American Airlines", "id": "Q32396"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1295_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Volkswagen Group from 1966 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Audi AG", "id": "Q23317"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1296_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Volkswagen Group from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Škoda Auto", "id": "Q29637"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1297_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Cathay Pacific from 2005 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Cathay Dragon", "id": "Q32436"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1298_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Rockstar Games between 2002 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Rockstar North", "id": "Q94893"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1299_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Phoenix Group between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Standard Life", "id": "Q471958"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1300_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of eBay from 2002 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "PayPal", "id": "Q483959"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1301_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Infineon Technologies between 2020 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cypress Semiconductor", "id": "Q478354"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1302_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Lille North of France University from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Artois University", "id": "Q475504"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1303_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Kering from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Gucci", "id": "Q178516"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1304_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Liberty Media from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One Group", "id": "Q174035"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1305_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of McLaren Technology Group between 1963 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "McLaren", "id": "Q172030"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1306_ab_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Simba Dickie Group from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Märklin", "id": "Q170127"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1307_ab_en", "question": "Cyryl Kozaczewski was an ambassador of which Embassy from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Polish Office in Taipei", "id": "Q30906461"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1308_ab_en", "question": "Cyryl Kozaczewski was an ambassador of which Embassy between 2012 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Embassy of Poland, Tokyo", "id": "Q30906141"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1309_ab_en", "question": "Seine was replaced by what during 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Paris", "id": "Q90"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1310_ab_en", "question": "Horch was replaced by what in 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "Auto Union", "id": "Q27152"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1311_ab_en", "question": "Zeevang was replaced by what during 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Edam-Volendam", "id": "Q9917"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1312_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Kirnitzschtal in 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Sebnitz", "id": "Q6483"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1313_ab_en", "question": "Spanish Sahara was replaced by what in the year of 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "Mauritania", "id": "Q1025"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1314_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Joutseno in the year of 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Lappeenranta", "id": "Q181854"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1315_ab_en", "question": "Seine was replaced by what in the year of 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Hauts-de-Seine", "id": "Q12543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1316_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Landeszentralbank in 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "Deutsche Bundesbank", "id": "Q162222"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1317_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Horch in 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "Audi AG", "id": "Q23317"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1318_ab_en", "question": "Perreuse was replaced by what during 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "Treigny", "id": "Q196379"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1319_ab_en", "question": "Entertainment and Leisure Software Publishers Association was replaced by what in 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Pan European Game Information", "id": "Q192916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1320_ab_en", "question": "Waterloo International railway station was replaced by what during 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "St Pancras railway station", "id": "Q720102"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1321_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Soviet Olympic Committee in 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Estonian Olympic Committee", "id": "Q775081"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1322_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Rijksmuseum van Natuurlijke Historie in 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Naturalis Biodiversity Center", "id": "Q641676"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1323_ab_en", "question": "What replaced University of Library and Information Science during 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Tsukuba", "id": "Q743615"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1324_ab_en", "question": "Bagneux was replaced by what during 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "Argenton-l'Église", "id": "Q1095133"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1325_ab_en", "question": "Shirokiya was replaced by what in 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "Tokyu Department Store", "id": "Q863194"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1326_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Eisenhower dollar in 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "Susan B. Anthony dollar", "id": "Q941062"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1327_ab_en", "question": "What replaced Soviet Olympic Committee during 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Latvian Olympic Committee", "id": "Q1185588"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1328_ab_en", "question": "What was USC Gould School of Law afflicted to between 1900 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Southern California", "id": "Q4614"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1329_ab_en", "question": "What was Pedro Szekely afflicted to between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Amazon", "id": "Q3884"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1330_ab_en", "question": "What was Wikimedia France afflicted to from 2008 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Wikimedia Foundation", "id": "Q180"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1331_ab_en", "question": "What was Tokuro Fujiwara afflicted to between 2005 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Capcom", "id": "Q14428"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1332_ab_en", "question": "What was Tokuro Fujiwara afflicted to from 1983 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Capcom", "id": "Q14428"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1333_ab_en", "question": "What was Daran Zheng afflicted to between 2010 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Hong Kong", "id": "Q15568"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1334_ab_en", "question": "What was Qun Zhang afflicted to between 1979 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Hong Kong", "id": "Q15568"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1335_ab_en", "question": "What was Daran Zheng afflicted to between 2018 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Hong Kong", "id": "Q15568"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1336_ab_en", "question": "What was Gerhard Bigalk afflicted to during 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "Condor Legion", "id": "Q153324"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1337_ab_en", "question": "What was Ethan Vishniac afflicted to from 1980 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "Princeton University", "id": "Q21578"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1338_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of South Prussia from 1795 to 1807?", "answer": [{"label": "Warsaw", "id": "Q270"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1339_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Poland from 1795 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Warsaw", "id": "Q270"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1340_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Canada from 1844 to 1849?", "answer": [{"label": "Montreal", "id": "Q340"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1341_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of South Prussia from 1793 to 1795?", "answer": [{"label": "Poznań", "id": "Q268"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1342_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Military Administration in Belgium and Northern France between 1940 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "City of Brussels", "id": "Q239"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1343_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Italy between 1946 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Rome", "id": "Q220"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1344_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Canada between 1849 and 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "Toronto", "id": "Q172"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1345_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Habsburg Netherlands between 1530 and 1581?", "answer": [{"label": "City of Brussels", "id": "Q239"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1346_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kingdom of Italy from 1871 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Rome", "id": "Q220"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1347_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Grand Duchy of Lithuania from 1323 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Vilnius", "id": "Q216"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1348_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Brandenburg between 1827 and 1843?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1349_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Switzerland from 1848 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bern", "id": "Q70"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1350_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of United States of America from 1800 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1351_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Abbasid Caliphate between 1261 and 1517?", "answer": [{"label": "Cairo", "id": "Q85"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1352_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Egyptian Fatimid Caliphate between 973 and 1171?", "answer": [{"label": "Cairo", "id": "Q85"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1353_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Francia between 508 and 768?", "answer": [{"label": "Paris", "id": "Q90"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1354_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of District of Columbia from 1790 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1355_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Brandenburg between 1918 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1356_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Germany from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1357_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Germany between 1994 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1358_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of United States of America from 1785 to 1790?", "answer": [{"label": "New York City", "id": "Q60"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1359_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of canton of Poissy between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Poissy", "id": "Q457"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1360_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kingdom of the Burgundians from 443 to 534?", "answer": [{"label": "Lyon", "id": "Q456"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1361_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kalmar Union between 1387 and 1523?", "answer": [{"label": "Oslo", "id": "Q585"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1362_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kingdom of Italy between 1861 and 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "Turin", "id": "Q495"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1363_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Portugal from 1385 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lisbon", "id": "Q597"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1364_ab_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Italy between 1861 and 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "Turin", "id": "Q495"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1365_ab_en", "question": "Scoot was operated by what between 2012 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 777", "id": "Q6425"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1366_ab_en", "question": "Japan Airlines was operated by what between 1985 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 767", "id": "Q6423"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1367_ab_en", "question": "Japan Airlines was operated by what from 1996 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 777", "id": "Q6425"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1368_ab_en", "question": "Swiss Global Air Lines was operated by what between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 777", "id": "Q6425"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1369_ab_en", "question": "All Nippon Airways was operated by what between 1995 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 777", "id": "Q6425"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1370_ab_en", "question": "Air Italy was operated by what between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 767", "id": "Q6423"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1371_ab_en", "question": "All Nippon Airways was operated by what from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 787 Dreamliner", "id": "Q6428"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1372_ab_en", "question": "Scoot was operated by what between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 787 Dreamliner", "id": "Q6428"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1373_ab_en", "question": "Air Italy was operated by what from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 787 Dreamliner", "id": "Q6428"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1374_ab_en", "question": "Yemenia was operated by what between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Airbus A310", "id": "Q6471"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1375_ab_en", "question": "British Overseas Airways Corporation was operated by what between 1960 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 707", "id": "Q6394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1376_ab_en", "question": "German Air Force was operated by what between 1968 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 707", "id": "Q6394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1377_ab_en", "question": "Braathens was operated by what between 1969 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 737", "id": "Q6387"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1378_ab_en", "question": "Braathens was operated by what between 1984 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 767", "id": "Q6423"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1379_ab_en", "question": "Alyemda was operated by what from 1977 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing 707", "id": "Q6394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1380_ab_en", "question": "Meta Platforms was operated by what between 2004 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Facebook", "id": "Q355"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1381_ab_en", "question": "Kalstar Aviation was operated by what between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "ATR 42", "id": "Q218637"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1382_ab_en", "question": "Japan Air Commuter was operated by what between 2017 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "ATR 42", "id": "Q218637"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1383_ab_en", "question": "Japan Air Commuter was operated by what from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Saab 340", "id": "Q277491"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1384_ab_en", "question": "Hokkaido Air System was operated by what between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Saab 340", "id": "Q277491"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1385_ab_en", "question": "East Japan Railway Company was operated by what between 1987 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Mito Line", "id": "Q302388"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1386_ab_en", "question": "British Overseas Airways Corporation was operated by what between 1949 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "Canadair North Star", "id": "Q302439"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1387_ab_en", "question": "Germania was operated by what between 2002 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Fokker 100", "id": "Q257298"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1388_ab_en", "question": "East Japan Railway Company was operated by what from 1987 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ryōmō Line", "id": "Q253391"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1389_ab_en", "question": "Austrian Airlines was operated by what between 2012 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Fokker 100", "id": "Q257298"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1390_ab_en", "question": "Jim Watkins was operated by what from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "2channel", "id": "Q222909"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1391_ab_en", "question": "German Air Force was operated by what from 1956 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Noratlas", "id": "Q651965"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1392_ab_en", "question": "Central Japan Railway Company was operated by what from 1987 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Tōkaidō Shinkansen", "id": "Q660895"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1393_ab_en", "question": "Swiss International Air Lines was operated by what between 2002 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "MD-11", "id": "Q62161"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1394_ab_en", "question": "Finnair was operated by what from 1990 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "MD-11", "id": "Q62161"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1395_ab_en", "question": "Cornell University Library was operated by what between 2001 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "arXiv", "id": "Q118398"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1396_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Rostec from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kamaz", "id": "Q30378"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1397_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Seoul Metropolitan Government between 1981 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Seoul Metro Corporation", "id": "Q20394"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1398_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Josh Harris from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Crystal Palace F.C.", "id": "Q19467"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1399_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Mike Ashley between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Newcastle United F.C.", "id": "Q18716"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1400_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Westinghouse Electric Corporation from 1995 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "CBS", "id": "Q43380"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1401_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Ronald Wayne in the year of 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "Apple", "id": "Q312"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1402_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Bernard Tapie between 1990 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "Adidas AG", "id": "Q3895"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1403_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Elon Musk from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "X", "id": "Q918"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1404_ab_en", "question": "Who owned Josh Harris between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Philadelphia 76ers", "id": "Q138089"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1405_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Bernard Tapie between 1986 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympique de Marseille", "id": "Q132885"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1406_ab_en", "question": "Who owned LVMH from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bulgari S.p.A.", "id": "Q752515"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1407_ab_en", "question": "Who owned General Electric from 1989 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Tungsram", "id": "Q689510"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1408_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Michael Kors from 2018 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Versace", "id": "Q696376"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1409_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Otto von Bismarck between 1871 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Friedrichsruh", "id": "Q695011"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1410_ab_en", "question": "Who owned CoStar Group from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Emporis", "id": "Q704560"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1411_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Ford Motor Company between 1938 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Mercury", "id": "Q613883"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1412_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of United Artists Corporation from 1969 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Pioneer Corporation", "id": "Q156034"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1413_ab_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Exor from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "The Economist Group", "id": "Q474153"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1414_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Spain between 1936 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "Francisco Franco", "id": "Q29179"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1415_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Civitas Schinesghe from 960 to 992?", "answer": [{"label": "Mieszko I", "id": "Q53435"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1416_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saint Lucia between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1417_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Poland between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Bronisław Komorowski", "id": "Q42939"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1418_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Indonesia from 1967 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Suharto", "id": "Q44819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1419_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Poland from 1989 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Wojciech Jaruzelski", "id": "Q55834"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1420_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of South Korea from 1998 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Kim Dae-jung", "id": "Q45785"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1421_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Georgia between 2008 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Mikheil Saakashvili", "id": "Q43330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1422_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Turkey between 2007 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Abdullah Gül", "id": "Q42852"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1423_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Ghana from 2012 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "John Dramani Mahama", "id": "Q50678"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1424_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of New Zealand between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1425_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Tuvalu between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1426_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Jersey between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1427_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Brazil from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Dilma Rousseff", "id": "Q40722"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1428_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Syria from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bashar al-Assad", "id": "Q44329"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1429_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Georgia between 2004 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Mikheil Saakashvili", "id": "Q43330"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1430_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Romania between 1881 and 1914?", "answer": [{"label": "Carol I of Romania", "id": "Q57146"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1431_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Solomon Islands between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1432_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1433_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saint Kitts and Nevis from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1434_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Papua New Guinea between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1435_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Antigua and Barbuda between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1436_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Nova Scotia from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1437_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of North Korea from 1948 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Kim Il-sung", "id": "Q41117"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1438_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Sweden between 1973 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Carl XVI Gustaf of Sweden", "id": "Q45068"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1439_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of India from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Pratibha Patil", "id": "Q47854"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1440_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Croatia between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Ivo Josipović", "id": "Q57258"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1441_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Sweden between 1907 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "Gustaf V of Sweden", "id": "Q52890"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1442_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Turkey from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Recep Tayyip Erdoğan", "id": "Q39259"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1443_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Jamaica between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1444_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of The Bahamas from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1445_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Mataram Sultanate between 1677 and 1703?", "answer": [{"label": "Amangkurat II of Mataram", "id": "Q47173"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1446_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Belize from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1447_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Australia between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1448_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saskatchewan from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1449_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Grenada from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1450_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Gibraltar between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1451_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Civitas Schinesghe between 992 and 1025?", "answer": [{"label": "Bolesław I the Brave", "id": "Q53436"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1452_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Romania between 1914 and 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "Ferdinand I of Romania", "id": "Q57165"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1453_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Isle of Man between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1454_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Falkland Islands from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1455_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of England between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1456_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Vatican City from 1929 to 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "Pius XI", "id": "Q42323"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1457_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Bailiwick of Guernsey between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1458_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Soviet Union from 1983 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "Yuri Andropov", "id": "Q44071"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1459_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of East Francia between 936 and 962?", "answer": [{"label": "Otto I the Great", "id": "Q43915"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1460_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Cook Islands from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1461_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Iran from 1979 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "Ruhollah Khomeini", "id": "Q38823"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1462_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Bulgaria from 2002 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Georgi Parvanov", "id": "Q57261"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1463_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of North Korea between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kim Jong-un", "id": "Q56226"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1464_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Niue from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1465_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Alberta between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Charles III of the United Kingdom", "id": "Q43274"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1466_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Cuba from 2008 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Raúl Castro", "id": "Q46809"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1467_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Weimar Republic between 1919 and 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "Friedrich Ebert", "id": "Q2646"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1468_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Germany between 1984 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Richard von Weizsäcker", "id": "Q2567"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1469_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Philippines from 1935 to 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "Manuel L. Quezon", "id": "Q1503"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1470_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Italy between 1962 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonio Segni", "id": "Q1240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1471_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Germany from 2010 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Christian Wulff", "id": "Q2540"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1472_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Austria from 1986 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "Kurt Waldheim", "id": "Q1260"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1473_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of France from 1981 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "François Mitterrand", "id": "Q2038"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1474_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Chile from 2018 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Sebastián Piñera", "id": "Q306"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1475_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Philippines between 1965 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "Ferdinand Marcos", "id": "Q1463"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1476_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Military dictatorship of Chile from 1973 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Augusto Pinochet", "id": "Q368"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1477_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of France from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Nicolas Sarkozy", "id": "Q329"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1478_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Chile between 2014 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Michelle Bachelet", "id": "Q320"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1479_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Kingdom of Bosnia from 1377 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "monarch", "id": "Q116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1480_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Vatican City from 1939 to 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "Pius XII", "id": "Q2604"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1481_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Italy between 1999 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Carlo Azeglio Ciampi", "id": "Q1224"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1482_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of Mongol Empire from 1206 to 1227?", "answer": [{"label": "Genghis Khan", "id": "Q720"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1483_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of German Empire from 1888 to 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "Wilhelm II", "id": "Q2677"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1484_ab_en", "question": "Who was the president of First French Empire between 1804 and 1814?", "answer": [{"label": "Napoleon", "id": "Q517"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1485_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Qt Group between 2008 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Nokia", "id": "Q1418"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1486_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Bell Labs from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nokia", "id": "Q1418"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1487_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Jeppesen from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1488_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Rocketdyne from 1966 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1489_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned DoubleClick from 2008 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1490_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Fitbit between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1491_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Google DeepMind between 2014 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1492_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Motorola Mobility between 2012 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1493_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Niantic from 2010 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1494_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of MD Helicopters between 1997 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Boeing", "id": "Q66"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1495_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Boston Dynamics between 2013 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Google", "id": "Q95"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1496_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Mobileye from 2017 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Intel", "id": "Q248"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1497_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Reality Labs between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Meta Platforms", "id": "Q380"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1498_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Wind River Systems between 2009 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Intel", "id": "Q248"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1499_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Mapillary AB from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Meta Platforms", "id": "Q380"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1500_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Gamepedia between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Fandom", "id": "Q17459"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1501_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Danger Close Games between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Microsoft", "id": "Q2283"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1502_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Jean Monnet University between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "University of Lyon", "id": "Q10176"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1503_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned German Labor Front from 1934 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nazi Party", "id": "Q7320"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1504_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Sikorsky Aircraft Corporation from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Lockheed Martin", "id": "Q7240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1505_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Tazo from 1999 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Starbucks", "id": "Q37158"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1506_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Mills College at Northeastern from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Northeastern University", "id": "Q37548"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1507_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Dehomag from 1924 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "IBM", "id": "Q37156"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1508_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of DreamWorks Records between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1509_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Red Hat from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "IBM", "id": "Q37156"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1510_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Okinawa General Bureau between 2001 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cabinet Office", "id": "Q6005"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1511_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Dacia from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Renault S.A.", "id": "Q6686"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1512_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Berliet from 1975 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Renault S.A.", "id": "Q6686"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1513_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Imperial Household Agency from 2001 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Cabinet Office", "id": "Q6005"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1514_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Glidden from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "PPG Industries", "id": "Q48754"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1515_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Monte Carlo Doualiya between 1996 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Radio France Internationale", "id": "Q19912"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1516_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Harman International Industries between 2017 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Samsung Electronics", "id": "Q20718"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1517_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Transportation Security Administration between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Department of Homeland Security", "id": "Q11231"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1518_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned United States Hydrographic Office from 1949 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Department of Defense", "id": "Q11209"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1519_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Federal Law Enforcement Training Center between 2003 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Department of Homeland Security", "id": "Q11231"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1520_ab_en", "question": "Which organization owned Bungie between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sony Interactive Entertainment", "id": "Q18594"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1521_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of FC Cincinnati from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Major League Soccer", "id": "Q18543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1522_ab_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Indiana Bell from 1920 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "AT&T", "id": "Q35476"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1523_ab_en", "question": "What was Design Museum used for from 1895 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "school", "id": "Q3914"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1524_ab_en", "question": "What was Hospital train used for between 1914 and 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1525_ab_en", "question": "What was Rimnersvallen used for between 1958 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "athletics", "id": "Q542"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1526_ab_en", "question": "Which league did AFC Bournemouth play for between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1527_ab_en", "question": "Which league did AFC Bournemouth play for between 2015 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1528_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Vincent Kompany play for between 2008 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1529_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Jonatan Johansson play for between 2000 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1530_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Romelu Lukaku play for from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1531_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Romelu Lukaku play for between 2011 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1532_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Gareth Bale play for between 2006 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1533_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Erik Lamela play for between 2013 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1534_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Leon Bailey play for between 2021 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1535_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Christian Pulisic play for from 2019 to 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1536_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Spezia Calcio play for between 2020 and 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1537_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Juventus FC play for from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1538_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Inter Milan play for between 1929 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1539_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Udinese Calcio play for from 1995 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1540_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Atalanta BC play for from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1541_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Cagliari Calcio play for between 2016 and 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1542_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Torino Football Club play for from 2012 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1543_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Juventus FC play for between 1929 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1544_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Dor Peretz play for from 2021 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1545_ab_en", "question": "Which league did ACF Fiorentina play for between 2004 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1546_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Genoa CFC play for between 2007 and 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1547_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Brescia Calcio play for from 2019 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1548_ab_en", "question": "Which league did AC Milan play for between 1983 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1549_ab_en", "question": "Which league did AC Monza play for between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1550_ab_en", "question": "Which league did David Beckham play for from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Major League Soccer", "id": "Q18543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1551_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Jeff Agoos play for between 1996 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Major League Soccer", "id": "Q18543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1552_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Celtic Warriors play for between 2003 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "United Rugby Championship", "id": "Q6002"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1553_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Oyonnax Rugby play for between 2013 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Top 14", "id": "Q5798"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1554_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Oyonnax Rugby play for between 2003 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Pro D2", "id": "Q5904"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1555_ab_en", "question": "Which league did ASM Clermont Auvergne play for between 1925 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Top 14", "id": "Q5798"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1556_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Cobi Jones play for between 1996 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Major League Soccer", "id": "Q18543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1557_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Philadelphia Union play for from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Major League Soccer", "id": "Q18543"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1558_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Cobi Jones play for between 1994 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Premier League", "id": "Q9448"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1559_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Cagliari Calcio play for between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1560_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Benevento Calcio play for between 2020 and 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1561_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Tajon Buchanan play for in the year of 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1562_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Erik Lamela play for from 2011 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1563_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Cristiano Ronaldo play for from 2018 to 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1564_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Elif Elmas play for between 2019 and 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1565_ab_en", "question": "Which league did Genoa CFC play for between 2023 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Serie A", "id": "Q15804"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1566_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Olympique Lyonnais between 1950 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Stade de Gerland", "id": "Q1980"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1567_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of France national association football team between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Stade de France", "id": "Q13205"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1568_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Heracles Almelo from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Erve Asito", "id": "Q11969"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1569_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of France national rugby union team between 1998 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Stade de France", "id": "Q13205"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1570_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Olympique Lyonnais from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Parc Olympique Lyonnais", "id": "Q8507"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1571_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Cagliari Calcio between 2012 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Stadio Is Arenas", "id": "Q24839"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1572_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of AFC Wimbledon during 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Kiyan Prince Foundation Stadium", "id": "Q31670"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1573_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Jokerit from 1997 to 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "Hartwall Arena", "id": "Q33176"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1574_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Ermis Aradippou FC from 2016 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonis Papadopoulos Stadium", "id": "Q268077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1575_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Nea Salamis Famagusta FC from 2004 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonis Papadopoulos Stadium", "id": "Q268077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1576_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Nea Salamis Famagusta FC between 1987 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonis Papadopoulos Stadium", "id": "Q268077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1577_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Anorthosis Famagusta FC between 1986 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Antonis Papadopoulos Stadium", "id": "Q268077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1578_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Golden State Warriors from 1996 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "SAP Center", "id": "Q261863"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1579_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Mystics from 1998 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Capital One Arena", "id": "Q223240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1580_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Girondins de Bordeaux from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Stade Bordeaux-Atlantique", "id": "Q252481"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1581_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Wizards from 1997 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Capital One Arena", "id": "Q223240"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1582_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of ADO Den Haag between 1925 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Zuiderpark Stadion", "id": "Q228630"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1583_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Los Angeles Rams between 1980 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Angel Stadium of Anaheim", "id": "Q531897"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1584_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Vancouver Canucks between 1995 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Rogers Arena", "id": "Q517318"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1585_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Vancouver Grizzlies from 1995 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "Rogers Arena", "id": "Q517318"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1586_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Nationals between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nationals Park", "id": "Q517545"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1587_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Montreal Canadiens between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bell Centre", "id": "Q522282"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1588_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Catalans Dragons during 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Montjuic Olympic Stadium", "id": "Q275715"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1589_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Minnesota Timberwolves from 1990 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Target Center", "id": "Q282675"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1590_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Sporting CP from 2003 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Estádio José Alvalade", "id": "Q287359"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1591_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Nationals from 1977 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympic Stadium of Montreal", "id": "Q285467"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1592_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Montreal Expos from 1977 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympic Stadium of Montreal", "id": "Q285467"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1593_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of RCD Mallorca from 1999 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Estadi Mallorca Son Moix", "id": "Q276163"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1594_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Porto from 2003 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Estádio do Dragão", "id": "Q271454"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1595_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Barcelona Dragons between 1991 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "Montjuic Olympic Stadium", "id": "Q275715"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1596_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Kansas City Chiefs from 1972 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Arrowhead Stadium", "id": "Q544553"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1597_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Sporting Kansas City from 1995 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Arrowhead Stadium", "id": "Q544553"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1598_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Indiana Fever between 2000 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Gainbridge Fieldhouse", "id": "Q545007"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1599_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Indiana Pacers between 1999 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Gainbridge Fieldhouse", "id": "Q545007"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1600_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Indiana Fever from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Gainbridge Fieldhouse", "id": "Q545007"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1601_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Portland Trail Blazers from 1970 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "Veterans Memorial Coliseum", "id": "Q549437"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1602_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Los Angeles Lakers between 1967 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "Kia Forum", "id": "Q639129"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1603_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chicago Bulls from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United Center", "id": "Q639975"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1604_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chicago Blackhawks from 1994 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United Center", "id": "Q639975"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1605_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chicago White Sox from 1991 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Guaranteed Rate Field", "id": "Q633613"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1606_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Valencia CF from 1923 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Mestalla Stadium", "id": "Q202762"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1607_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Juventus FC between 1990 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Stadio delle Alpi", "id": "Q215493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1608_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of AFC Ajax between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Johan Cruyff Arena", "id": "Q207109"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1609_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Detroit Pistons from 1978 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "Pontiac Silverdome", "id": "Q211662"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1610_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Juventus FC from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino", "id": "Q214629"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1611_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Bayern Munich from 2005 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Allianz Arena", "id": "Q127429"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1612_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Catalans Dragons in the year of 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Wembley Stadium", "id": "Q128468"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1613_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Edmonton Elks between 1978 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Commonwealth Stadium", "id": "Q130381"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1614_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Israel national football team from 1964 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bloomfield Stadium", "id": "Q130150"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1615_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Bayern Munich between 1972 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "Olympic Stadium of Munich", "id": "Q131610"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1616_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Erie SeaWolves between 1995 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "UPMC Park", "id": "Q128810"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1617_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Orix Buffaloes from 2005 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kyocera Dome Osaka", "id": "Q128836"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1618_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Real Madrid Baloncesto from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Community of Madrid Sports Centre", "id": "Q539019"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1619_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Brooklyn Nets between 1981 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Meadowlands Arena", "id": "Q538218"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1620_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Real Madrid Baloncesto from 1986 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Community of Madrid Sports Centre", "id": "Q539019"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1621_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of San Antonio Spurs from 2002 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Frost Bank Center", "id": "Q298573"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1622_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of AZ Alkmaar from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "AFAS Stadion", "id": "Q291590"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1623_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chiba Lotte Marines from 1992 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "ZOZO Marine Stadium", "id": "Q486192"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1624_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Orlando Magic from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Amway Center", "id": "Q481795"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1625_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Orlando Magic from 1989 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Amway Arena", "id": "Q481794"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1626_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Roda JC Kerkrade from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Parkstad Limburg Stadion", "id": "Q476674"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1627_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of France national rugby union team between 1973 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "Parc des Princes", "id": "Q193431"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1628_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of San Diego State Aztecs football from 2020 to 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Dignity Health Sports Park", "id": "Q200684"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1629_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Los Angeles Chargers between 2017 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "Dignity Health Sports Park", "id": "Q200684"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1630_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Golden State Warriors from 1962 to 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "Cow Palace", "id": "Q604015"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1631_ab_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Memphis Grizzlies between 2004 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "FedExForum", "id": "Q641212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1632_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Sovremennik between 1836 and 1837?", "answer": [{"label": "Alexander Pushkin", "id": "Q7200"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1633_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Crash Bandicoot from 1996 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "Sony Interactive Entertainment", "id": "Q18594"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1634_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Neues Deutschland between 1946 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "Socialist Unity Party of Germany", "id": "Q49750"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1635_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Byzantinische Zeitschrift between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "De Gruyter", "id": "Q98818"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1636_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of IEEE Annals of the History of Computing from 1992 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers", "id": "Q131566"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1637_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of New York World from 1883 to 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "Joseph Pulitzer", "id": "Q173417"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1638_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of IBM Journal of Research and Development from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers", "id": "Q131566"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1639_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Zork between 1986 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "Activision Publishing", "id": "Q200491"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1640_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Tumor Biology between 2010 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Springer Science+Business Media", "id": "Q176916"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1641_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Virtual International Authority File between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "OCLC, Inc.", "id": "Q190593"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1642_ab_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Crash Bandicoot from 2008 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Activision Publishing", "id": "Q200491"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1643_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of SimCity between 1906 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "San Francisco", "id": "Q62"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1644_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of SimCity between 1972 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Bern", "id": "Q70"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1645_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of The Tin Drum between 1943 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "Paris", "id": "Q90"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1646_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Khovanshchina from 1682 to 1689?", "answer": [{"label": "Moscow", "id": "Q649"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1647_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Anne of the Island from 1883 to 1887?", "answer": [{"label": "Prince Edward Island", "id": "Q1978"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1648_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Anne of Green Gables from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "Prince Edward Island", "id": "Q1978"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1649_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Anne of the Island between 1883 and 1887?", "answer": [{"label": "Nova Scotia", "id": "Q1952"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1650_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Naked Among Wolves during 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "Buchenwald concentration camp", "id": "Q152802"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1651_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Robinson Crusoe between 1651 and 1654?", "answer": [{"label": "Salé", "id": "Q466046"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1652_ab_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of The Tin Drum in the year of 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "canton of Cabourg", "id": "Q1724677"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1653_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Wendell Ford belong to between 1944 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1654_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Alvin York between 1917 and 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1655_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Hal Moore between 1945 and 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1656_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Colonel Sanders belong to from 1906 to 1907?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1657_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Douglas MacArthur between 1903 and 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1658_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Frank Lautenberg from 1942 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1659_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Norman Mineta belong to between 1953 and 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1660_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of David Glantz between 1963 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1661_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Ted Kennedy from 1951 to 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1662_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Theodore Roosevelt belong to from 1882 to 1886?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1663_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Nipsey Russell from 1941 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1664_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Rodney Frelinghuysen belong to between 1969 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1665_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Greg Steube belong to from 2004 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1666_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Robert Duvall from 1953 to 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1667_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of James Joseph Dresnok from 1958 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1668_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Ronald Reagan between 1942 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1669_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Adam Clymer belong to from 1961 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1670_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did William Roth belong to between 1943 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1671_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Rob Simmons belong to between 1965 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1672_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did John Conyers belong to from 1950 to 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1673_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Wint Smith belong to between 1917 and 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1674_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Doug Bereuter from 1963 to 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1675_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Henry Wharton Conway belong to from 1812 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1676_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Wint Smith belong to between 1941 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1677_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Tim Conway between 1956 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1678_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Allen West belong to from 1982 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1679_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Emanuel Celler between 1942 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1680_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Malcolm Forbes belong to from 1942 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1681_ab_en", "question": "Which military brach did Joe Medicine Crow belong to between 1943 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1682_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Ty Carter between 2008 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1683_ab_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Truman Smith between 1935 and 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Army", "id": "Q9212"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1684_ab_en", "question": "Who was the rector of Humboldt University of Berlin from 1990 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "Heinrich Fink", "id": "Q121809"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1685_ab_en", "question": "Who was the rector of Heidelberg University during 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "Franz Boll", "id": "Q107670"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1686_ab_en", "question": "Who was the rector of Heidelberg University from 1925 to 1926?", "answer": [{"label": "Heinrich Liebmann", "id": "Q104487"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1687_ab_en", "question": "What was Hans Beimler engaged or conflicted with from 1914 to 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1688_ab_en", "question": "What was Constantin Cristescu engaged or conflicted with from 1916 to 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1689_ab_en", "question": "What was Constantin Prezan engaged or conflicted with between 1916 and 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1690_ab_en", "question": "What was Karl Gebhardt engaged or conflicted with from 1917 to 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1691_ab_en", "question": "What was Aristide Razu engaged or conflicted with from 1916 to 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1692_ab_en", "question": "What was Wilhelm Leuschner engaged or conflicted with between 1916 and 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "World War I", "id": "Q361"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1693_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Vindobona between 1957 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "Berlin", "id": "Q64"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1694_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Istanbul Express between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Skopje", "id": "Q384"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1695_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Capitol Limited between 1966 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington Union Station", "id": "Q3570"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1696_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Vindobona from 1957 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Vienna", "id": "Q1741"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1697_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Seibu Shinjuku Line between 1952 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Seibu-Shinjuku Station", "id": "Q167299"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1698_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Seoul Metropolitan Subway Seohae Line in 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Ilsan Station", "id": "Q59868"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1699_ab_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Nasuno from 1995 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Kōriyama Station", "id": "Q385879"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1700_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Little Lulu Show from 1998 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "TV Globo", "id": "Q3587"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1701_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of YOUniverse during 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Facebook", "id": "Q355"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1702_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of YOUniverse during 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "YouTube", "id": "Q866"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1703_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Go On Girl Star Search in the year of 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Facebook", "id": "Q355"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1704_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Go On Girl Star Search during 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "YouTube", "id": "Q866"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1705_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of BlackBoxTV Presents from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "YouTube", "id": "Q866"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1706_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Parenthood between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1707_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Knight Rider from 1982 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1708_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of ALF from 1986 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1709_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Fame between 1982 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1710_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Scrubs from 2001 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1711_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Medical Investigation between 2004 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1712_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of National Geographic Explorer from 2001 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "MSNBC", "id": "Q13973"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1713_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Imus in the Morning from 1996 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "MSNBC", "id": "Q13973"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1714_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Las Vegas between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1715_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Alfred Hitchcock Presents between 1960 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1716_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Alfred Hitchcock Presents from 1964 to 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1717_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Medium from 2005 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1718_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Holocaust in the year of 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1719_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Office between 2005 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1720_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Deal or No Deal between 2005 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1721_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Blindspot between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1722_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Player from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1723_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Best Time Ever with Neil Patrick Harris from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1724_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Late Night with Seth Meyers between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1725_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Truth Be Told from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1726_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Heroes Reborn between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1727_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of JAG from 1995 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1728_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Phantom of the Opera in the year of 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1729_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Constantine from 2014 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1730_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1731_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Silver Spoons between 1982 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1732_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Knight Rider between 2008 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1733_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Hazel between 1961 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1734_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Taxi from 1982 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1735_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Friday Night Lights from 2006 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1736_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Little House on the Prairie between 1974 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1737_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The High Chaparral from 1967 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1738_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Late Night with Jimmy Fallon from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1739_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Marco Polo from 1982 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1740_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of In the Heat of the Night between 1988 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1741_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The West Wing from 1999 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1742_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Santa Barbara from 1984 to 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1743_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Meet the Press between 1947 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1744_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Saved by the Bell from 1989 to 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1745_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Saturday Night Live between 1975 and 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1746_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Ed from 2000 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1747_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of V from 1984 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1748_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Apprentice from 2004 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1749_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of American Odyssey in 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1750_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Hardball with Chris Matthews between 1999 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "MSNBC", "id": "Q13973"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1751_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Morning Joe between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "MSNBC", "id": "Q13973"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1752_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of All My Children during 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "iTunes", "id": "Q9589"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1753_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Countdown with Keith Olbermann from 2003 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "MSNBC", "id": "Q13973"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1754_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Countdown with Keith Olbermann between 2011 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Current TV", "id": "Q19666"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1755_ab_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Aquarius between 2015 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "NBC", "id": "Q13974"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1756_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Panther Chan from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1757_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Chris Martin between 2013 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1758_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Alan Stivell between 1985 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1759_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mon Laferte from 2003 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1760_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Rip Slyme between 2001 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1761_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Three Days Grace from 2003 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Jive Records", "id": "Q27184"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1762_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mike Oldfield between 1992 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1763_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Shiga Lin between 2010 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1764_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Alec Benjamin from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1765_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of David Guetta from 2013 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Warner Music Group", "id": "Q21077"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1766_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lady Gaga between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1767_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Chris Martin between 2011 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1768_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Miki Imai between 2015 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1769_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lady Gaga from 2007 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Cherrytree Records", "id": "Q21091"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1770_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of SG Lewis between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1771_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kaija Koo from 1999 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1772_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Passpo between 2011 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1773_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Olavi Uusivirta between 2003 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1774_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Martin Garrix from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1775_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Cecilia Cheung from 1999 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1776_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Loreen from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1777_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kei from 2014 to 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "Woollim Entertainment", "id": "Q50596"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1778_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Ismael Serrano from 1998 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1779_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Nina Nesbitt between 2012 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1780_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mon Laferte between 2011 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "independent music", "id": "Q42201"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1781_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lee Jaijin from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1782_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of CL between 2009 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1783_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mura Masa between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Universal Music Group", "id": "Q38903"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1784_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lee Hi from 2012 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1785_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Annie Cordy from 1998 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Sony Group", "id": "Q41187"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1786_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of John Cale in the year of 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "Beggars Banquet Records", "id": "Q126039"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1787_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Selena Gomez from 2007 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "Walt Disney Records", "id": "Q54860"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1788_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Sechs Kies between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1789_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of One between 2015 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1790_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Hilary Duff between 2001 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Walt Disney Records", "id": "Q54860"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1791_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Jang Su Won between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1792_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kim Jaeduck from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1793_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kang Sung Hun between 2016 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "YG Entertainment", "id": "Q50595"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1794_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of MC Solaar from 1991 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "Polydor Records", "id": "Q155152"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1795_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Borknagar between 1996 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Century Media Records", "id": "Q158867"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1796_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mura Masa between 2014 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Polydor Records", "id": "Q155152"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1797_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Bee Gees from 1967 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Polydor Records", "id": "Q155152"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1798_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Dadju from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Polydor Records", "id": "Q155152"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1799_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Omnium Gatherum between 2016 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Century Media Records", "id": "Q158867"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1800_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Insomnium between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Century Media Records", "id": "Q158867"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1801_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Madonna from 1982 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Sire", "id": "Q165711"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1802_ab_en", "question": "What was the record label of Maurizio Pollini from 1971 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Deutsche Grammophon", "id": "Q168407"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1803_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Stardew Valley use from 2019 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Android", "id": "Q94"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1804_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did The Room use between 2013 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Android", "id": "Q94"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1805_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Stardew Valley use from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Linux", "id": "Q388"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1806_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Touhou Project use between 2002 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Microsoft Windows", "id": "Q1406"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1807_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Dead Cells use from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Microsoft Windows", "id": "Q1406"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1808_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Bad North use from 2018 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Microsoft Windows", "id": "Q1406"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1809_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Pingus use from 2010 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Microsoft Windows", "id": "Q1406"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1810_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Pingus use from 2011 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "macOS", "id": "Q14116"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1811_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did The Room use between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "iOS", "id": "Q48493"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1812_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Discord use from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Xbox", "id": "Q132020"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1813_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Touhou Project use between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "NEC PC-9800 series", "id": "Q183505"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1814_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Potlatch use from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Adobe AIR", "id": "Q360310"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1815_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Jurassic World Evolution use from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nintendo Switch", "id": "Q19610114"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1816_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Factorio use from 2022 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nintendo Switch", "id": "Q19610114"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1817_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did Shadowverse use from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Nintendo Switch", "id": "Q19610114"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1818_ab_en", "question": "Which platform did MicroPython use from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "RISC-V", "id": "Q17637401"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1819_ab_en", "question": "Which child of Hemma was born in the year of 832?", "answer": [{"label": "Louis III the Younger", "id": "Q160190"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1820_ab_en", "question": "Which child of Hemma was born during 830?", "answer": [{"label": "Carloman of Bavaria", "id": "Q157084"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1821_ab_en", "question": "Which child of Miyamoto Musashi was born in 1623?", "answer": [{"label": "Miyamoto Iori", "id": "Q6884333"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1822_ab_en", "question": "Which child of Henry Fok was born in 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Timothy Fok", "id": "Q7807201"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1823_ab_en", "question": "Which child of Henry Fok was born in 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "Ian Fok", "id": "Q9372313"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1824_ab_en", "question": "Which child of Run Run Shaw was born in the year of 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "Shaw Vee-Meng", "id": "Q15912932"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1825_ab_en", "question": "Albrecht Brandi was a crew member of what from 1941 to 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "U-552", "id": "Q656087"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1826_ab_en", "question": "Which crew did Engelbert Endrass belong to during 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "Admiral Scheer", "id": "Q160712"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1827_ab_en", "question": "Engelbert Endrass was a crew member of what from 1938 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "U-47", "id": "Q638673"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1828_ab_en", "question": "Which crew did Albrecht Brandi belong to from 1935 to 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "German cruiser Karlsruhe", "id": "Q663558"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1829_ab_en", "question": "Victor Oehrn was a crew member of what between 1927 and 1929?", "answer": [{"label": "SMS Berlin", "id": "Q876226"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1830_ab_en", "question": "Victor Oehrn was a crew member of what during 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "German cruiser Königsberg", "id": "Q689046"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1831_ab_en", "question": "Felix von Bendemann was a crew member of what between 1874 and 1876?", "answer": [{"label": "SMS Gazelle", "id": "Q2206862"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1832_ab_en", "question": "Heinrich Liebe was a crew member of what between 1931 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "SMS Schleswig-Holstein", "id": "Q170363"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1833_ab_en", "question": "Albert Lauzemis was a crew member of what between 1941 and 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "U-68", "id": "Q549416"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1834_ab_en", "question": "Sian Proctor was a crew member of what from 2021 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Inspiration4", "id": "Q105209621"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1835_ab_en", "question": "What was the family name of Camille Grammer between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Meyer", "id": "Q46767"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1836_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Viktor Ullmann between 1942 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "Theresienstadt Ghetto", "id": "Q15111616"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1837_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Al Capone between 1932 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "United States Penitentiary, Atlanta", "id": "Q2495408"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1838_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Al Capone in 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "Federal Correctional Institution, Terminal Island", "id": "Q5440156"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1839_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Donald Tsang in 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Stanley Prison", "id": "Q986106"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1840_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Albert Speer between 1947 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "Spandau Prison", "id": "Q168700"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1841_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Tommy Chong between 2003 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "Taft Correctional Institution", "id": "Q26831364"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1842_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Jefferson Davis from 1865 to 1867?", "answer": [{"label": "Fort Monroe", "id": "Q1438639"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1843_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Sergei Magnitsky between 2008 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Butyrka prison", "id": "Q1018222"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1844_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Viktor Frankl from 1942 to 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "Theresienstadt Ghetto", "id": "Q15111616"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1845_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Hubert Robert in 1794?", "answer": [{"label": "Prison Saint-Lazare", "id": "Q1498170"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1846_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Hubert Robert from 1793 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Sainte-Pélagie Prison", "id": "Q1641986"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1847_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Shyne from 2001 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "Clinton Correctional Facility", "id": "Q1637388"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1848_ab_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Naftaly Frenkel between 1923 and 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "Solovki prison camp", "id": "Q2443828"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1849_ab_en", "question": "Where was Idol charted in in the year of 2023?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan Hot 100", "id": "Q848647"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1850_ab_en", "question": "Where was Machine Head charted in in the year of 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1851_ab_en", "question": "Where was Machine Head charted in in the year of 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1852_ab_en", "question": "Where was Jesus Christ Superstar charted in during 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1853_ab_en", "question": "Where was Imagine charted in in 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1854_ab_en", "question": "Where was Jesus Christ Superstar charted in in the year of 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1855_ab_en", "question": "Where was Shaft charted in during 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1856_ab_en", "question": "Where was All Things Must Pass charted in in the year of 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1857_ab_en", "question": "Where was No Time to Die charted in from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Singles Chart", "id": "Q193259"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1858_ab_en", "question": "Where was Tapestry charted in during 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1859_ab_en", "question": "Where was We Found Love charted in in 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1860_ab_en", "question": "Where was American Pie charted in during 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard 200", "id": "Q188819"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1861_ab_en", "question": "Where was Old Town Road charted in during 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1862_ab_en", "question": "Where was One More Night charted in in 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1863_ab_en", "question": "Where was Set Fire to the Rain charted in in the year of 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1864_ab_en", "question": "Where was Sunflower charted in during 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1865_ab_en", "question": "Where was Diamonds charted in during 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1866_ab_en", "question": "Where was Shallow charted in in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1867_ab_en", "question": "Where was We Are Young charted in in the year of 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1868_ab_en", "question": "Where was Somebody That I Used to Know charted in during 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1869_ab_en", "question": "Where was Locked Out of Heaven charted in in the year of 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1870_ab_en", "question": "Where was Whistle charted in in the year of 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1871_ab_en", "question": "Where was No Time to Die charted in from 2020 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1872_ab_en", "question": "Where was Truth Hurts charted in in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1873_ab_en", "question": "Where was Lose You to Love Me charted in in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1874_ab_en", "question": "Where was We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together charted in in the year of 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1875_ab_en", "question": "Where was Sucker charted in in the year of 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Billboard Hot 100", "id": "Q180072"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1876_ab_en", "question": "Where was Ram charted in during 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1877_ab_en", "question": "Where was Bridge over Troubled Water charted in in the year of 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1878_ab_en", "question": "Where was Bridge over Troubled Water charted in in the year of 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1879_ab_en", "question": "Where was Imagine charted in in 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1880_ab_en", "question": "Where was All Things Must Pass charted in during 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1881_ab_en", "question": "Where was Led Zeppelin IV charted in during 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "UK Albums Chart", "id": "Q719415"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1882_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in World Curling Federation in 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1883_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in International Organization of Journalists during 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Norway", "id": "Q20"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1884_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in World Curling Federation in the year of 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1885_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in International Convention on Load Lines in 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Norway", "id": "Q20"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1886_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in International Organization of Journalists during 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "Belgium", "id": "Q31"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1887_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in National Popular Vote Interstate Compact in 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "Washington, D.C.", "id": "Q61"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1888_ab_en", "question": "Who participated in National Popular Vote Interstate Compact in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "Illinois", "id": "Q1204"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1889_ab_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for Gauss from 1904 to 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1890_ab_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for HMCS Bonaventure from 1957 to 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1891_ab_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for HSC Natchan Rera between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1892_ab_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for ADV Ocean Shield from 2010 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "Norway", "id": "Q20"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1893_ab_en", "question": "United States Marine Forces Europe and Africa applied to which place between 2008 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Africa", "id": "Q15"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1894_ab_en", "question": "Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement applied to which place from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1895_ab_en", "question": "Mint applied to which place between 2010 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Canada", "id": "Q16"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1896_ab_en", "question": "Regional Comprehensive Economic Partnership applied to which place between 2022 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1897_ab_en", "question": "Protocol against the Illicit Manufacturing of and Trafficking in Firearms applied to which place from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1898_ab_en", "question": "limited liability partnership applied to which place from 2005 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Japan", "id": "Q17"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1899_ab_en", "question": "Forestry Commission applied to which place from 1919 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "England", "id": "Q21"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1900_ab_en", "question": "Forestry Commission applied to which place between 1919 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "Scotland", "id": "Q22"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1901_ab_en", "question": "Hymn of Riego applied to which place between 1820 and 1822?", "answer": [{"label": "Spain", "id": "Q29"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1902_ab_en", "question": "limited liability partnership applied to which place between 1991 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1903_ab_en", "question": "Miranda warning applied to which place between 1966 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United States of America", "id": "Q30"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1904_ab_en", "question": "Senate of Finland applied to which place between 1917 and 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "Finland", "id": "Q33"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1905_ab_en", "question": "Prespa agreement applied to which place between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Greece", "id": "Q41"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1906_ab_en", "question": "Protocol III applied to which place from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Switzerland", "id": "Q39"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1907_ab_en", "question": "French university master applied to which place from 1966 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "France", "id": "Q142"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1908_ab_en", "question": "Charter of the Forest applied to which place between 1927 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United Kingdom", "id": "Q145"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1909_ab_en", "question": "Parliament of the United Kingdom applied to which place between 1927 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United Kingdom", "id": "Q145"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1910_ab_en", "question": "Act of the Parliament of the United Kingdom applied to which place between 1927 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "United Kingdom", "id": "Q145"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1911_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Deborah Levi participate between 2012 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "athletics", "id": "Q542"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1912_ab_en", "question": "What sport did World Athletics participate from 1912 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "athletics", "id": "Q542"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1913_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Carlyle Eubank participate between 2002 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "athletics", "id": "Q542"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1914_ab_en", "question": "What sport did FC Winterthur participate between 1923 and 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "tennis", "id": "Q847"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1915_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Adriano Panatta participate from 1969 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "tennis", "id": "Q847"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1916_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Ashleigh Barty participate from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "tennis", "id": "Q847"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1917_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Tennis Borussia Berlin participate between 1902 and 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "tennis", "id": "Q847"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1918_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Hard Rock Stadium participate between 2019 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "tennis", "id": "Q847"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1919_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Ellis Park Stadium participate from 1931 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "tennis", "id": "Q847"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1920_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Rio Haryanto participate in the year of 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1921_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Nello Pagani participate in 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1922_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Fittipaldi Automotive participate from 1975 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1923_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Paul di Resta participate from 2011 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1924_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Charles Leclerc participate between 2018 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1925_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Sebastian Vettel participate from 2007 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1926_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Fittipaldi FD participate from 1975 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1927_ab_en", "question": "What sport did All American Racers participate between 1966 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1928_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Alex Zanardi participate from 1991 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1929_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Marcus Ericsson participate from 2014 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1930_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Surtees participate between 1970 and 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1931_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Esteban Ocon participate from 2016 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1932_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Stoffel Vandoorne participate between 2016 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1933_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Geoff Duke participate in 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1934_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Brendon Hartley participate from 2017 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1935_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Max Verstappen participate from 2015 to 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1936_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Pascal Wehrlein participate between 2016 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1937_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Jolyon Palmer participate between 2016 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "Formula One", "id": "Q1968"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1938_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Keepmoat Stadium participate between 2007 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "association football", "id": "Q2736"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1939_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Jarry Park Stadium participate between 1966 and 2024?", "answer": [{"label": "association football", "id": "Q2736"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1940_ab_en", "question": "What sport did Estadio GEBA participate from 1908 to 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "association football", "id": "Q2736"}], "type": "answerable", "cls_target": "Yes", "lan": "en"}]